Hello, folks at home.
I'm 100 yards from the top of Mt. Everest.
Yet there's a part of me
that can't wait to end this silly vacation...
...and get back to work,
where the real challenges await.
Shouldn't you take your age
into consideration, sir?
After all, you're 82 years old.
Am I 82?
These numbers mean nothing to me.
My journey through life has just begun.
Sir! Sir!
-Oota tells me the storm's getting worse.
-Very, very bad.
We must abandon our ascent and
go down the mountain immediately.
We're so very close to the top,
Mr. Puffy Jacket Man.
I'm heading down now, sir.
I advise you to do the same.
All right, so be it.
See you at the staff meeting on Monday.
And I'll bring the Krispy Kremes!
There, once again, the sad footage
we've been watching all day.
A beloved visionary who turned a single
radio station into a global media empire...
...Preston Blake, dead at 82. More after this.
You're watching the Blake Broadcasting Network.
The stock of Blake Media,
the parent company of this network...
...plunged this morning
on the news of Blake's death...
...but bounced back after a statement
by Blake's longtime number 2, Chuck Cedar.
All the king's horses and all the king's men...
...couldn't save Preston Blake
from becoming a human Popsicle.
And sources indicate that Blake, who was
single and had no children, left no will.
So who inherits Blake's 49 percent stake
in the company's stock...
...valued at $40 billion?
We'll discuss that with people close
to Blake, including his longtime barber...
...on tomorrow's lnside Access.
Until then, I'm Mac McGrath.
-Are we clear?
-Clear!
Babe? Where's Babe?
-I'll come over and choke you to death.
-Babe!
I got to go.
Freaking barber!
That's the best you could get me?
People tell everything to their barbers.
He's been his closest confidant
for more than 20 years.
I'm not putting this guy on the air.
Get me something better and get it quick.
Or it's your ass.
Did we find this heir yet?
We should be getting that information
via fax any minute now.
I have lawyers looking through birth records...
...in all 50 states, Puerto Rico and Guam.
In fact, we have a little pool going.
Guam's paying off at 1000-1.
Is this a joke to you?
Some genetic lottery winner
now controls the fate of this company.
No, I agree. It's troubling.
Troubling? Your beard is troubling.
Your pipe is troubling.
Your yellow teeth are really troubling.
But if I lose control of this company,
it'll be catastrophic.
Does anyone know a Dr. Mendlesohn?
Congratulations, you have a spastic colon.
That would explain a lot.
"Longfellow Deeds."
Chuck, I think we're there.
My God, it's all green.
Look at that thing. Fighter pilot on your left.
Got that sucker!
You guys lost?
We're looking for somebody: Longfellow Deeds.
Is that Deeds' first name?
If the Deeds you're referring to
is Longfellow Deeds...
...then yes, that is Deeds' first name.
I don't know Deeds' first name. Maybe it's Greg.
-Maybe it's Longfellow.
-Maybe.
But I don't know. I know another guy
named Greg. You want me to call him?
No! Thank you.
Please, just tell us where Deeds lives.
All right, don't get all hyperactive.
I'll take you straight to him.
Step right in, fellows.
-He lives at a pizzeria?
-You can't live in a pizzeria.
He lives upstairs. He owns it.
Excuse me. Is Mr. Deeds around?
No, I'm sorry, he's out making deliveries.
The regular delivery guy called in sick.
-But you don't look too sick, Murph.
-I forgot I was faking sick today.
-You two tricked me into coming here.
-Murph, put on an apron and give me a hand.
You guys played me like a fiddle. Touch?
Is Mrs. Deeds around?
Mrs. Deeds?
I don't think that poor boy ever had a date.
-Do you know when he'll be back?
-Before lunch is out. Today's Card Day.
-Card Day?
-Deeds writes greeting cards.
Every Monday, he tries out a few
and then he chooses one...
...and sends it to one of the big card companies.
Now, he hasn't sold any yet, but...
...he will.
You guys need anything else here?
"To my sweetheart
"I love you completely, with all my soul
"Without you I'm nothing, a butterless roll"
That's good.
Like that, gentlemen?
Hallmark said it showed potential,
which is pretty cool.
-Longfellow Deeds?
-Just call me Deeds, pal.
Easy with that Longfellow stuff.
Chuck Cedar, CEO.
Cecil Anderson, General Counsel of Blake Media.
Handshakes are for strangers.
We hug around here, buddy.
What's up? Welcome to town.
Come on, don't be shy.
I like that beard. Abe Lincoln-style.
Have a seat, boys.
-Murph!
-Deeds?
-I thought you were sick today.
-That was a lie, pal.
You fooled me.
-I did?
-Yeah.
-Mr. Deeds?
-Just Deeds.
You sounded so sick on the phone.
You're good. Do that sick voice again.
Deeds, I can't come to work today.
I think I got strep throat.
That's unbelievable.
You could be a radio actor or something.
-Thanks, buddy.
-Sure.
Hey, Deeds. Read a card already.
I got to get back on duty.
I'd better get up there.
Good meeting you, gentlemen.
Mr. Deeds, does the name Preston Blake
mean anything to you?
Mom's maiden name was Blake.
Only one this week, but I got a feeling
it'll end my losing streak with Hallmark.
Preston Blake was your mother's uncle.
You're kidding me, I got an uncle?
Awesome. How's he doing?
He's dead.
Oh, no. If there's anything I can do....
Deeds! Deeds!
I'll be right with you guys.
When Mr. Blake died,
he left an enormous fortune.
$40 billion. He left it all...
...to you, Deeds.
Wait a minute.
What are you talking about, you got
to get back on duty? You're not a cop.
You're right.
I got this down at the costume shop.
But it can't hurt to pretend.
What a wisenheimer!
Okay, everybody, it's showtime.
I call this "50th Anniversary Card."
Which is quite a feat nowadays.
"Fifty years have passed by
with laughter and tears
"Do you remember when we went to the zoo
"and that time we drank all the beers"
Beers!
"I promise to love you for 50 years more
"Even when your bosoms sag down to the floor"
That was awesome! How's he do it?
It looks like you won't have
to deliver pizza anymore, Deeds.
You're a very rich man.
What's that got to do with delivering pizzas?
Ladies! The top one is yours.
-Thank you, Deeds.
-Of course.
-Yummy!
-So, Deeds, what's new?
I found out I have an uncle, but he died.
That's too bad.
-He gave me $40 billion, though.
-Well, that's nice.
Oh, yeah!
Don't you go and spend it all
on some fancy record player.
I won't.
Who are your friends, Deeds?
I'm sorry.
Chuck, Cecil, this is Jane, Kitty and Sue.
-Pleasure to meet you, Cecil.
-Pleasure's all mine, Kitty.
Or should I just say, "Meow"?
Keep it in your pants, Anderson.
-Now, why am I inheriting this money?
-You're Mr. Blake's closest living relative.
-Really? He had nobody else?
-Nope, that's it.
Gosh, I never even met the guy.
Would you hold this for a second?
Mr. Wetherley. How you doing, pal?
Very well, Deeds. Just going to the pharmacy.
Well, let me get you there a little quicker.
-How's your wife?
-She's fine.
-Terrific. Say hi for me.
-I will.
Okay. Here you go.
-Thanks for the lift, Deeds.
-You got it.
We need you to come back to New York with us.
Just for a few days.
We're drawing up some papers
you'll need to sign.
What kind of papers?
Technically, you've inherited
300 million shares of Blake Media, lnc.
Chuck and I, along with
some of the partners, will buy that stock...
...for $40 billion,
which we've had to borrow from various--
Who cares about the financial mumbo jumbo?
We need a little time
to dot the t's and cross the i's.
And while we're doing that,
we need you to stay away from the press.
The media frenzy will die down
in a couple weeks but until then....
You don't want reporters crawling
all over this lovely little town, do you?
Oh, no!
-Crazy Eyes!
-What?
How you doing, pal?
I got your pizza, just the way you like it.
Oh, yes!
French fries and Oreos.
You know me all too well, Deeds.
What are you in for?
I'm doing a one-nighter
for biting Ed the mailman.
The guy was trying to cast a spell on me,
like a wizard.
-Are you sure about that?
-I don't know. Maybe he was just waving.
-Who are your friends?
-This is Chuck and Cecil from New York.
I don't like them.
Okay. Nice seeing you.
I've never been to New York before.
I suppose I could check out the sights.
-Give me an hour to pack, okay?
-You got it.
I'll be the first guy to leave here since
Jimmy McNally went to Disney World.
See you later, everybody!
Tomorrow is "Kids Eat For Free" Day.
Don't forget to clean the highchairs.
Don't worry, I'll take care of everything.
-Go, have a good time!
-I'll miss you.
'Bye, Jan. Smell you later, Murph.
-Give us a card!
-Yeah!
"On my way to the big city for a business trip
"Never, ever left Mandrake Falls before
Ain't that a pip
"But while I'm gone, I know I'll miss you all a lot"
"So bring your rich butt back here
and buy us all a shot"
You got it, pal!
Take it easy.
The biggest story of the year
and we've got nothing?
Do you people want to be tabloid journalists?
Because I don't think so.
You've got to be ruthless. When I started out...
...I slept in Tom and Roseanne's dumpster
for two days...
-...disguised as a giant carton of ice cream.
-I got it!
My source at Blake says
the company helicopter...
...took off from there this afternoon
with two male passengers aboard...
-...headed for Mandrake Falls.
-Where?
Some little hick-ass town in New Hampshire.
But now they're on their way back
with three male passengers.
-That's one more!
-Duh!
That third guy's our heir. Nice work, Marty.
They were supposed to arrive
at Blake Media at 5:00.
But they made an unscheduled stop
in Connecticut.
I'm so happy I got the Big Bacon Classic.
Thanks for stopping. This is unbelievable.
-Happy to do it.
-How's that Frosty treating you, Cecil?
You got some on your beard. I'm just kidding.
I got him big time, man.
I'm going on the air in two hours' time.
And I want that guy's life story by then.
I'm talking to you, Jim.
And I'm also talking to you, Babe. Babe?
Where the hell's Babe?
You missed another staff meeting. Mac's pissed.
He won't be pissed when I crack this Blake story.
-What do you got?
-Nothing. Do you have anything?
I'll have a lot more in a few hours.
You got to be a pal.
I need this story.
I'm flat broke and Mac is going to fire me.
How're you flat broke?
You make more money than anyone here.
-What did you blow it on?
-Shoes.
I'll tell you everything I know
over lunch tomorrow...
...as long as your club promoter boyfriend...
...doesn't try to run me over
with his motorcycle again.
You're safe there.
Ken and I are kind of taking a break.
Really? So he moved out?
Babe, what are you staying here for?
I have a spare bedroom.
We tried that once, remember?
I woke up and you were standing
over my bed, breathing heavily.
I was having an asthma attack.
I couldn't find my puffer.
Easy, fellows.
The Biggie Fries are making a comeback.
You guys football fans? The Pats
could take the conference this year.
The Dolphins are overrated
and the Jets are choke artists.
I wouldn't say that, Mr. Deeds.
-Just Deeds. Why is that, though?
-You own the Jets, Deeds.
I do?
That sucks.
I hope they don't play the Pats in the playoffs
or I'll have to kill myself.
I'm still very worried about this.
What do you got in that pipe, hashish?
You're paranoid.
-This guy's perfect for us.
-What if he won't sell us his shares?
If I got Blake to trust me with his company...
...I can get this moron to do the same.
Look at him.
That's right, Anderson.
Enough!
Party pooper.
Holy cow!
What's up, New York?
It's an honor to come
to the greatest city in the world!
Congratulations, Deeds, you're now
the most eligible bachelor in New York.
I don't want to meet a girl
just because I'm wicked rich.
That's nice, but let's see
how you stick to your guns...
...once you've paid a visit to one
of our many fine gentlemen's clubs.
What?
My father saved my mother.
She was figure skating and fell through the ice.
I always thought I'd meet
a girl the same way. Bullspit like that.
Then I'll just keep a lookout
for ladies in distress, as it were.
-That'd be nice.
-Hey, Mandrake Falls!
Security, stop that guy!
Stop! Come back!
He'll get $100,000 for the picture.
It'll be on the news in an hour.
He deserves it with those
James Bond moves he just pulled.
No, he deserves to get his throat cut,
the filthy spy. Come on, let's go.
So this is where my uncle lived?
Yes, sir. For the last 35 years
of his astonishing life.
-You kind of snuck up on me there.
-I am very, very sneaky, sir.
I see that. My name is Deeds.
I am Emilio, sir. I am your servant.
Servant? I don't want a servant,
but if you want to be my friend, I'll take that.
Friends.
Yes, good friends.
Would you like to go down to your apartment?
I'm sure it's been an exhausting day.
-That okay with you, Chuck?
-You'll be safe there.
It'll take us a couple days
to draw up the papers for you to sign.
-Go make yourself at home.
-Terrific.
-Later.
-I will be with you shortly, sir.
You got it. Nice to meet you. I'm Deeds.
-I'm Reuben, sir.
-This is a wicked nice elevator.
Keep an eye on him, Emilio. Or it's your ass.
It's nice to see you too, sir.
So how's the elevator business
treating you, Reuben?
It has its ups and downs.
All right! All right!
That was good.
Jeesum crow, how'd you get down here so fast?
Sneaky-sneaky, sir. Right this way.
Wow.
Is something the matter, sir?
-That's an echo, sir.
-Yeah, you try it.
-Me, sir?
-It's a lot of fun.
Come on, you can do it louder than that.
-Serious.
-Thank you, sir.
Hey, buddy, how you doing?
You want to give it a shot?
Nice.
You guys want to join us? Make a weird noise.
That was a great time. Well, I'm tired.
I'd like to go to sleep.
-This way.
-Thank you very much. Good night, everyone.
Good night.
You just going to lie there
and let the Post take your story?
What's up, New York?
He had a water fountain in his room. I love it.
That's Hawaiian Punch.
He adored...
...Hawaiian Punch.
Wow! You kind of just snuck up on me there.
I fear you're underestimating the sneakiness, sir.
I guess I was. What are you doing down there?
I am assisting you with your sock change.
You'd change my socks for me?
You don't got to do that. Stand up.
Thank you.
Besides, you don't want
to have to touch my right foot.
I got wicked bad frostbite when I was
in the Scouts. Check it out.
Pretty messed up, huh?
The hideousness of that foot
will haunt my dreams forever.
Yeah, I've heard that before.
But the weird thing is I got no feeling left in it.
So you could jump on it and it wouldn't hurt me.
-Go ahead, jump on it.
-I'd really rather not, sir.
Please jump on my foot.
I didn't feel that.
What else you got? Get that
fireplace poker and whack my foot.
-Do I absolutely have to?
-It's going to be fun. Just grab it.
All my friends do this when they're wasted.
Come on.
Go ahead, give it a whack.
-Nothing.
-Really?
Isn't that sick?
Didn't feel that. Isn't that awesome? Go ahead.
Nothing.
You're starting to like it, aren't you?
Chop that wood!
That's it!
You're sick! You're sick!
Why would you do that?
I'm just kidding you, pal.
-You had me going there.
-I saw your face, you were like....
I got to find out from Cedar and Anderson
what I'm supposed to do today.
So could you take that out of my foot?
I'm nailed to the ground.
There you go.
I must insist on absolute secrecy
regarding this discussion...
...till I've officially acquired Mr. Blake's shares.
If that's acceptable,
then as far as I'm concerned...
...you've just bought 2,000 radio stations.
Good morning.
Deeds.
What's up?
Doing a little business.
This room's an echo room, too.
I'm sure you guys already knew that.
May I help you?
I just wanted to see
if there's anything I should do today.
I think we've got everything under control.
There's got to be something. Until I sign
those papers I own this place, right?
What?
Ladies and gentlemen,
pardon me a moment, please.
Of course.
What's up, buddy? I was dreaming
about Frosties all last night. You?
I tried to make my own at home,
but it wasn't the same.
Deeds.
Every stockholder, large and small,
has a say in the operation of this company.
They have this say
at the annual stockholders' meeting.
The other 364 days of the year,
the officers of the company, like me...
-...run the show.
-You mean now that my uncle's gone.
Yeah, and it's not all fun and games.
This company is a player on so many levels
and in so many areas...
...that running it is literally a 24-hour-a-day job.
I only got three hours of sleep last night.
Then it's actually a 21-hour-a-day job, huh?
Move it, lady.
I don't give a damn about no meeting.
Mr. Cedar, I am sorry--
I passed for 3,500 yards last season
and I ain't gonna touch a football...
...until you get off your fat, rich asses
and renegotiate my bullshit contract.
Easy with the language, buddy.
There are ladies present.
Shut the hell up, rich boy!
I want more money, or you all can just suck my--
I warned you.
You went down like a sack of potatoes,
I'll tell you that much. Come on.
Come on, big man. Upsy-daisy.
Mesdames and Gentlemen, football!
What's the problem with your contract?
I figured if I played well,
I'd renegotiate and get more money.
If you didn't play well,
could we renegotiate and pay you less?
Shit, no!
I mean, no.
Doesn't seem fair to me.
-He led the League in touchdown passes.
-That's okay, Chuck. I got this one.
Listen, fellows, I want more money...
...or I ain't even gonna play another down.
Well, we'll have to let you go then.
-"Let me go"?
-Yeah, you're fired.
So can I sign with another team?
You can do anything.
I suggest you change your attitude...
...or nobody will want to work with you.
'Bye.
Deeds.
Kevin won the Heisman Trophy two years ago.
He is our best player.
-Don't worry, he'll be back.
-Biggest mistake of your lives!
This thing is cool.
Why don't you get out and enjoy the city?
Everything's fine here. Take that with you.
I'll leave it here. That's all right.
But call me if you need me.
-Absolutely.
-Thanks. Love you, Anderson.
All you guys, I noticed you were French.
The opposite of bonjour to you.
You look so hot as a blond.
It's not too streaky?
I feel like he did it really streaky.
I love it, but let me go undercover.
This could get dangerous.
He said he likes ladies in distress,
not men who wear too much cologne.
-There he is.
-Thanks for the tour.
-You're welcome.
-Hidden cameras on, ready? Molest me.
-Molest me!
-You got it!
-God, help!
-Give it to me.
-Help, I'm being mugged!
-All right!
Help! Help! I'm being mugged!
-Stop it!
-Good luck. See you at the office.
-Don't worry, I'll get him.
-Oh, shit!
Stop right there.
Come on!
What's your problem, pal?
Come up here.
Got your pocketbook. Get a job, pal.
Miss! Miss!
-Are you okay?
-What happened?
Let me help you up.
All right, now. All right.
Ma'am, you were just the victim
of a New York City mugger.
As I suspected, he was a coward and a weakling.
And also wore more cologne
than any man should wear.
-I got this back for you, though.
-Thank you.
-Can I take you to the hospital?
-No, no.
I'll be all right.
I just feel a little dizzy and violated.
I'm fine.
Please, let me take you to the emergency room.
I'm sure I'll be all right. I just need to...
...perhaps walk it off or....
-Could you?
-Sure.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
My name is Pam. Pam Dawson.
My name is Deeds. I'm not from here.
I'm just visiting.
Where do you hail from?
Mandrake Falls, New Hampshire.
Just a little town nobody's ever heard of.
I'm from a little town like that.
-In lowa.
-Is that right? What part?
Winchestertonfieldville.
Yes, the small town
of Winchestertonfieldville, lowa.
I'm sorry.
-What are you doing in New York?
-I'm a school nurse.
-There's no way you're a school nurse.
-Why, don't you believe me?
You're too nice to be a school nurse.
My school nurse was so mean,
every time I'd tell her I had a tummy ache...
...she'd send me back to my class
and say, "Stop whining."
-But that's awful!
-Well, I said it every day.
I missed my mother.
That's sweet.
Miss Dawson?
How would you like to maybe go out...
...and have a New York City dinner with me?
Golly.
That sounds wonderful.
-It does?
-Yeah.
-Let's do it, then.
-Okay.
Damn you, Old Spice.
So you run this pizza place
and you have your poetry.
What brings you to the big city?
Actually, I just inherited $40 billion.
Well, that's nice, but I think anything
over $30 billion is just gravy.
I like that.
Your hair is very blond and pretty.
I'm of Swedish ancestry.
-Really?
-Yes.
My grandfather was in ABBA.
ABBA, the band?
Excuse me,
do you get any famous people in here?
Famous, rich, powerful.
Really? We don't get
any famous people in Mandrake Falls.
Stephen King stopped by
our gas station one time...
...but everyone was too scared to talk to him.
I'd imagine he'd be very spooky.
Jake, the gas station attendant,
made eye contact with him.
That night he lost 200 pounds.
Wow.
Your chicken parmesan should be ready soon.
Okay, buddy. I saw a couple over there.
It's their anniversary.
Give them this. Don't say it's from us, though.
This is like $20,000.
Tell them it was a restaurant giveaway
or something. Thanks, buddy.
That's an awfully nice way
to start spending your money.
-Is that who I think it is?
-Who?
Preston Blake's nephew, the $40-billion man.
We have to meet him. Dave?
Gosh, I hope that mugger got home okay.
-Mr. Deeds.
-Yeah.
Mr. Simonds would like
to invite you to join his party.
Why is that?
Just to enjoy the pleasure of your company.
Wow, that's pretty cool of him.
That was a very nice hug, Deeds.
It's wicked nice of you to invite us over.
This is awesome.
-Have we met?
-Not unless you have a sick kid.
You're a very important man
in this town now, Mr. Deeds.
I don't know about that.
I sing at the Metropolitan Opera...
...and Blake Media contributes
50 percent of our budget.
So, on behalf of the opera:
"Thank you"
That was awesome!
You shouldn't thank me, though.
You should thank my great-uncle.
He was an interesting man.
I served on the board
of the Guggenheim with him.
Really? I'm not sure what that is,
but good luck with it.
I'd love to write a piece on you
for The New Yorker.
What's The New Yorker?
It's a magazine.
With essays, witty cartoons.
I read the Mandrake Falls Gazette
and they got some cartoons in there also.
You know who's a riot? That Beetle Bailey guy.
He's always wearing his hat and doing his thing.
But it is an honor to meet
a real writer like you, George.
I've been trying
to get my stuff published for years...
...but Hallmark is one tough cookie to crack.
-Hallmark?
-He writes greeting cards.
-I try.
-You must share one with us.
-I don't know about that, Mr. French.
-Who's Mr. French?
-Doesn't he look like Mr. French?
-I've never heard of him.
Come on.
All right, I'll give you one.
This is a Mother's Day card I've been working on.
"Mom, you are the one
who brought me to planet Earth
"You are the one who suffered
through my 14-hour birth
"You are the one who made lemonade for me
after I'd come back from play
"I love you, Mom,
so have a wicked nice Mother's Day"
Something like that.
-An instant classic!
-"Genius, genius, genius"
Do you write your poems with a crayon?
It's amazing!
I see why you brought me here.
To goof on me, huh?
-Don't be silly, Deeds.
-Pipe down, George.
I may seem funny to you,
but if you came to Mandrake Falls...
...you might seem funny to us.
Only nobody would laugh at you...
...and make you feel stupid,
that wouldn't be good manners.
Maybe my poems aren't that great,
but I know some people who like them.
Anyways, it's the best I can do.
We're going to get going.
Sorry about that, Pam.
I hope I didn't embarrass you.
And if it wasn't for Miss Dawson being here,
I'd knock your heads in.
I don't mind.
Okay.
"No"
I think I just shat myself.
How would you like to see the sights now?
I just need to powder my nose.
That would be great. I'll get your coat.
Hey, buddy, this will pay for everything
I damaged. Sorry about that.
-Good to meet you guys.
-Thank you.
God, that was good stuff.
I want a raise, Mac.
Hey, man! What's up?
Holy cannoli, you're John McEnroe!
I saw what you did to those guys
making fun of you. Nice work.
You know what it's like to get riled up
don't you, Johnny Mac?
-That I do.
-I'm Deeds, by the way.
Deeds, nice to meet you.
You got to let me buy you a drink.
Miss Dawson, this is John McEnroe.
-Miss Dawson, nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you, too.
I promised Miss Dawson I'd take her sightseeing.
The sights are great.
I've seen the sights. I love the sights.
Let me show you a New York
most people will never see.
-That okay with you, Miss Dawson?
-Sounds like fun!
Here's to a big night on the town.
What happened?
Here are some aspirins, Mr. Deeds.
They make your head seem smaller.
-How did I get in these pajamas?
-I changed you.
I was very gentle, sir.
I think I drank all the alcohol in Manhattan
last night.
And you nearly succeeded,
according to Miss Dawson.
Miss Dawson! I don't even remember
taking her home. Is she okay?
I took the liberty of sending her off
in the company limousine.
She was a lady in distress and I helped her.
Dreamt about her last night.
Usually, when you get blackout drunk
you don't dream.
So I read.
What's up, Chuck?
America's newest billionaire...
-...stupid and drunk.
-What's this?
It was quite a night for Longfellow Deeds.
They'll know my name is Longfellow.
After punching out some society types...
...Deeds joined forces with the original
bad boy of tennis, John McEnroe.
And stupidity won in straight sets.
How'd they get that footage?
Watch out, Johnny!
What kind of driving is that?
You're a fucking disgrace!
No, sir. You're a disgrace.
-We did it, man!
-Johnny McEnroe!
Look at Deedsy hanging out with McEnroe!
That's awesome!
I love the Beach Boys.
Here I go, here I go.
This is not the kind of attention
we need right now.
What do you mean?
For the moment you're the largest stockholder...
...and people might think
any instability you show...
...may equal instability in the company.
My bad.
My bad. My bad.
Okay. Okay.
-My bad.
-Okay.
Shall I call your car, Mr. Cedar,
to take you to the funeral?
What funeral?
Your great-uncle's funeral.
-His funeral's today?
-Today, yes.
I'll go get my suit on.
-Cute, bigmouth.
-Sir?
As soon as that moron goes back
to Cowpie Falls...
...you are out of here
on your fat Puerto Rican ass.
I hail from Spain, sir.
Ol?
Now, Brother Preston is soaring
with eagles high above.
Because he lived a life of love.
Yes, he's flying way up high...
...because he was a supercool guy.
He's gone away, too soon, it seems...
...leaving behind his unfinished dreams.
This guy could make a fortune
writing greeting cards.
Yes, we remember Preston Blake...
...a man with faith no man could shake.
A strength no man could break.
A character no man could fake.
For goodness sake, let's eat some cake.
Amen.
Excuse me, Reverend, that was a grand slam.
That part with soaring with the eagles
gave me goosebumps.
-Thank you, my brother.
-My friend got me a mug for my birthday.
It says, "It's hard to soar with the eagles
when you're surrounded by turkeys."
But what you said was better.
It's all good.
Rest in peace, Preston.
That concludes today's service.
I actually thought I would say something.
Deedsy was always the best speaker in school.
Deedsy?
That's some job, by the way, Your Majesty.
I thought we were watching Scooby-Doo.
Hi, my name is Deeds.
I was Preston Blake's great-nephew.
I wrote a poem for him
on my way over here, in my head.
And I'm going to recite it for you.
I didn't realize I'd be following
the rhyme-master Reverend Sharpton.
But here we go anyways.
"You climbed mountains and built skyscrapers
"You made TV shows and put out newspapers
"You were wicked good at doing stocks
"You liked it
when Emilio would change your socks
"We never hung out and that makes me sad
"AII the good times we could've had"
Nice rhyme.
"But when I die, Uncle Preston,
you'd better say, 'Cheers!'
"'Cause me and you are hanging
at the pearly gates
"I'll bring the beers, I'll bring the beers"
He's good.
Amen.
I know this is supposed to be
a closed casket, but where I come from...
...we feel it's good to see the body
for the grieving process, so....
Sorry about that! I'll keep this sucker closed.
He's still pretty frozen.
Almost there.
I'll keep an eye on the company for you.
Love you.
Nice meeting you. Thanks for the apartment.
That was freaky.
Everybody drive home safe.
Man, this guy is in way over his head.
-Take care.
-You'll see him tonight?
Yes, I'm calling around 4:00.
That's when I get off work.
Remember, I'm Pam Dawson, virgin school nurse
from Winchestertonfieldville, lowa.
That's priceless.
You, a virgin.
-All right, thank you.
-Excuse me, sir.
-I told him he could have that.
-Thanks.
Right on. Nice seeing you.
You need to use our bathroom,
come back and use it, okay?
-Will do!
-All right.
How do you think I did at the funeral today?
You spoke beautifully, sir.
I still feel bad.
I snapped my uncle's hand off
when I put him back in the casket.
Lucky for him, he was dead, sir.
Even though his face was frozen that way...
...it looked to me like he was a happy guy.
Am I right?
-He truly was.
-Come on, sit down, please.
And I got to hang out with him, just like this...
...almost every day for 30 years.
What did you guys talk about?
We spoke of life, love, art, wine, business.
I learned much from him.
-I bet you miss him, too.
-I do.
He was like a parent to me.
You see, I never knew my father, and Mama...
...she passed while giving the birth to me.
-You want some Cocoa Pebbles?
-No, thanks.
I have much work to do.
-Thanks. You don't have to do that.
-Enjoy your Pebbles.
One more thing.
Your great-uncle did not let me
change his socks for him, either.
I like feet.
I do not know why.
Hello.
Hi, Deeds? It's Pam. Pam Dawson.
I'm so happy you called.
I'm wicked sorry about last night.
I don't drink very often.
I thought you held your liquor very well.
Unfortunately, I couldn't hold it for too long.
That's okay. I didn't really like that skirt anyway.
I'm getting a call on the other line.
Can you hang on for a second?
-Sure.
-Thank you.
Hello.
Mr. Deeds, this is Kevin Ward,
the quarterback you punched.
What's up, buddy?
I wanted to say that I was thinking it over
and I'd like to live up to my word.
And I'd like to win you a Super Bowl.
-That's terrific, pal.
-And my daddy wants to speak to you.
Deeds. Buddy Ward here, Kevin's daddy.
How you doing, Mr. Ward?
I just want to thank you
for teaching my boy a lesson.
He's a good kid. He just has to watch
his language in front of ladies.
I'll remind Kevin where he comes from.
That sounds terrific.
You used foul language in front of a lady?
No, Daddy, no!
Pam.
Still here.
How's it going? You at work?
-Yep, here in the nurse's office.
-Any customers?
Customers? Oh, sick kids.
Well, little Billy Barty's here.
-You're not feeling too good, Billy?
-Miss Dawson, my tummy hurts.
Why don't you just lay back and relax?
That was nice. Good job.
I've got too much doo-doo in my underpants.
Make the stinky go away.
Well, you sound like
you got your hands full, so...
...I'll just come out with it.
How would you like
to do something with me tonight?
I'd love to do something with you.
Great.
We can't go out drinking.
I got our company in trouble.
That's okay.
I was brought up never to drink alcohol.
Not even rum raisin ice cream.
I like that. I'll think of something good.
See you tonight.
Okay. 'Bye.
I got to try this.
Was that awesome?
Am I out or safe?
I'm with you.
What is this? My great-uncle's personal journal.
-Should I read it?
-Family.
Family, safe, good.
All right, have a good night. My back hurts!
-Nice doing business with you.
-Thank you.
Thanks for the bikes.
What are you gonna do with your $20,000?
Buy a giraffe.
Quit school.
Good idea, school is for fools. Look at me!
The park is beautiful.
These trees, they remind you
of Winchestertonfieldville at all?
Oh, yes. Very much so.
What was it like growing up there?
It was great.
I remember walking down
to the corner drugstore...
...and getting malted milkshakes.
What was your house like?
We had this big Victorian.
Right off Main Street.
-Blue shutters and a big red door.
-All right.
-And a tire swing in the front yard.
-I love it.
And I remember the time I fell out of
old Boo Radley's apple tree...
...and broke my arm.
And my father, before he passed away...
...from the disease of the lepers...
...he came and he scooped me up
and he ran me all the way to Dr. Pepper's.
Dr. Pepper.
Yeah.
I'm glad that guy was around.
-Want to sit down?
-Sure.
-Thank you.
-My pleasure.
I was reading my great-uncle's journal
on my way over to you.
And, when he was age 9...
...he wrote that he had the only family
on the block with a radio...
...and he was dreaming
of becoming a disc jockey someday.
A disc jockey?
You know, when I was a kid,
I wanted to be a news reporter.
I used to go around interviewing everyone...
...and writing notes
in my little Holly Hobby notebook.
People didn't like that. I got beat up a lot.
-Do you remember their names?
-No, it was a long time ago.
But my grandma said to me:
"One day you'll grow up
and work for 60 Minutes...
"...and make a difference in the world."
You do make a difference in the world,
every day. You're a school nurse.
Anyways, this is what happened to my uncle.
Later on in his life, he'd go
to this radio station that he owned...
...at 3:00 in the morning and DJ for an hour.
That's great.
So, don't give up hope.
You'll be a reporter someday.
If you really want to.
That would be nice.
-Jeesum Crow, a fire!
-A fire?
-We should help.
-We should?
-Let's get going.
-To the fire?
-Fifi, get over here right now.
-Come on, we'll catch you.
Go away! I can't leave without my kitties.
They're all I got.
Crazy lady!
-Oh, babies, where are you?
-Up there now, get going!
Longfellow Deeds, Mandrake Falls
volunteer fire chief. I'll be up there in a jiff.
-He's crazy.
-He's going up there right now, though.
-Look at him.
-Where's he going?
Watch it, man!
-Sully, who's that guy up there?
-I don't know.
He says he's from
the Mandrake Falls Fire Department.
-How's he climb like that?
-He must have monkey blood in him.
It's an honor to work
with New York's bravest guys.
Be careful!
-I'll get you.
-Babies, where are you?
-Ma'am!
-Lord, it's hot in here.
-Kitties, come to Mommy.
-Calm down. Everything will be all right.
Okay, but I'm not leaving without my kitties.
-How many do you got?
-Seven.
Holy shit! Let's get cracking.
-I apologize for the language.
-Apology accepted.
-Fire excites me.
-Knock yourself out.
-Come here.
-That's Freddy.
-Here we go!
-Oh, my children!
-Nice catch, Pam!
-Good throw, Deeds!
-That's Frobo. Thank you, darling.
-Coming at you, boys.
I'll take that.
-There's a lot more.
-Okay, okay.
Holy shit, it's a cat!
Full snap. I got you, kitty.
Nice grab!
One more to go.
Fifi, where are you?
-I think I found Fifi.
-Oh, good!
Hang in there, buddy!
I got it!
Okay, let's do this together.
Be careful!
All right, they do it all the time. Here we go.
Oh, shit!
Deeds.
I'm okay.
Are you okay?
Yes, I am. Thanks to you!
You're hurting me!
Longfellow Deeds is at it again.
His latest victim, Coretta Keeling...
...whose only crime
was loving her cats too much.
And letting Deeds find out about it.
-I'll get you!
-Go away!
-I love it.
-Here comes two!
-Cat killer!
-After he finished with her cats...
...he turned his sights on Miss Keeling herself.
My God!
That's not what I shot.
Has Longfellow Deeds been locked up?
Of course not.
While the rest of us obey the law,
rich playboys like himself get to laugh at it.
Longfellow Deeds. Our jackass of the week.
What the hell? Who edited that?
I did. Your first cut was great,
but I needed to spice it up a bit.
The truth was a great story.
He saved that woman and her seven cats.
-He was heroic!
-Heroic is nice.
-Depraved and insane is better.
-Hell, yeah!
This footage you're getting, gorgeous.
Keep it coming!
God, how can we do this to such a sweet guy?
Sweet? Sweet?
Look at me!
Was he sweet when he gave me
the most savage beating of my life?
-You were mugging me!
-Babe!
No one is as good as this guy's pretending to be.
Don't be a sucker.
He doesn't deserve this.
He doesn't deserve you.
My neck!
I feel like an idiot.
They made me look like a fool, Jan.
I was thinking of going down
to that lnside Access place...
...and giving Mac McGrath
the beating of a lifetime.
That sounds like fun,
but don't stoop to their level.
You're better than that, Deedsy.
So hang in there.
And know that we are always here for you.
Thanks, Jan.
My uncle really built an amazing company.
Because of him, 50,000 people have jobs.
And he always tried to do the right thing.
Well, he does sound amazing.
But don't forget, he was related to you.
Enough about that. Tell me more about this girl.
She's nice, a small-town kid, like me.
Deedsy, you sick-ass mo' fo'....
You got to tap that
before she starts boning other guys, kid.
Boo-Yah!
He thinks it's you! He thinks it's you!
-Let's go, Cedar. Put some steam on it, kid.
-Here it comes.
He's trying to kill me. You're good at this.
When you asked me to play,
I thought you'd done this before.
No, Johnny McEnroe said it was wicked easy.
Plus, it was my uncle's favorite game, right?
-How'd you know that?
-I read it in his diary.
Really?
I didn't know he kept a diary.
Sorry about that, dude.
It's okay. He's a new member.
Ball boy.
Ball boy!
All right, baby, I'm ready for you.
You okay?
-Not a problem.
-Anderson, you liked that, didn't you?
I did.
Listen, Deeds, I got some good news.
Those papers will be ready to sign tomorrow.
So you can relax knowing
your uncle's company'll be in good hands...
...and you can go home $40 billion richer.
I was thinking about
maybe sticking around here...
-...and going to some meetings with you.
-What?
Fault!
I figured I could learn, like this tennis thing.
I swear to God, I'm not trying to do that.
I don't got to sell my shares right away, do I?
Plus, I met this girl, Cedar.
I swear to God, I think she's the one.
That's wonderful for you.
That got you right in the throat, huh?
Got to ask you, though, if it hits you,
is it my point or yours?
-Yours.
-I'm winning then, I guess.
"Deeds info, meet in shower"?
Sweet Jesus!
Who are you? And what do you want to tell me?
I'm a junior producer at lnside Access.
I have information that will help you
get Deeds out of town. Interested?
Very. Provided the information is good
and you stop soaping your ass.
-You know Deeds' girlfriend?
-The school nurse.
Not quite.
Lucy, bring me the overnights.
J.D. will tell you where they are.
Hey. What the hell are you doing in my chair?
Chuck Cedar.
I think you and I could help each other out.
-You excited about this trip?
-I'm so excited.
-Where are you taking me?
-I told you, that's a surprise.
Well?
"Winchestertonfieldville, lowa."
You got to be shitting me.
I never heard you curse before.
I'm that excited!
All you Winchestertonfieldvillians,
recognize this little girl?
I'll give you a hint.
"I fell out of Boo Radley's apple tree...
"...and my arm is killing me!"
Come on, it's little Pammy Dawson!
Hello.
You related to Bill Dawson?
Yes, he's my relative.
I think I remember you.
Did you used to have a hump on your back?
-Yes, that was me. I had a slight hump.
-Really?
This was no slight hump.
The girl I'm thinking of looked like
she had a damn beach ball on her back.
Okay, it was a huge hump
and I'm a little sensitive about it.
Look, Martha, it's Quasimodo, all growed up.
How wonderful! I thought you died.
She actually became a school nurse.
-You're a nurse?
-Yes.
What should I do about this?
-I would call Dr. Pepper.
-Who?
It was so great seeing everybody again.
We're going to leave now.
'Bye.
-Hi, mailman.
-'Morning.
How you doing?
Oh, my God, there it is.
Blue shutters, red door, tire swing.
That's your house, isn't it?
Wouldn't you know it?
Come on.
How you guys doing? You know who she is?
She used to live in this house
when she was a little girl.
It's true.
You live here and she used to live here.
You're practically cousins.
So many memories.
Where to begin?
This is our fireplace...
...where my dad would build fires...
...out of wood.
And this is the dining room,
where we would have our meals...
...made of food.
And this was my brother's room.
My parents hated my brother.
My daddy built this house
with his bare hands six years ago.
Your daddy is a liar.
How come you--
He's choking. We should go.
-Help.
-What are you talking about?
-You're the nurse, help him.
-Save him!
-Stand back, kids.
-He's gonna die!
-Take him to the hospital!
-Smack it out!
-Save him!
-Get it out of him!
Save him, please!
-That was amazing.
-Thank you.
I saved his life.
You're my hero, Nurse Dawson.
Thank you, thank you.
-Good parking job, buddy.
-Thanks, Deeds.
Testing, testing.
I had such a wonderful time.
Thank you for such a great day.
-Thanks for showing me your town.
-I hope sometime to see your hometown.
Maybe someday this will be my new hometown.
Deeds.
-There's something I have to tell you.
-What's the matter?
What?
Go back to New Hampshire and enjoy being rich.
Just...
...don't let anyone hurt you anymore, okay?
Sucker.
Pam.
I made a card for you.
It's kind of dumb.
I never worked on anything harder, though,
so don't laugh at me.
Remember we went to the restaurant
that first night...
...and you ordered chicken parmesan?
So I drew you a plate.
There's the chicken and the cheese...
...and the linguini. That took me
a long time with the squigglies.
It's beautiful.
There's a poem inside for you.
"Hard to breathe, feels like floating
"So full of love my heart's exploding
"Mouth is dry, hands are shaking
"My heart is yours for the taking
"Acting weird, not myself
"Dancing around like the Keebler elf"
That was funny.
"Finally time for this poor schlub
"to know how it feels to fall in lub"
I couldn't think of anything else
that rhymes with "schlub."
"Rub" and "tub" didn't work.
I'm sorry, Deeds.
-I'm really sorry.
-Don't be sorry, that was unbelievable.
Hi, Mrs. Finch.... Atticus.
Sleep well.
-Al, I'm gonna walk home.
-Okay, Deeds.
I love New York!
Nobody cares!
I'm in love with him.
I'm going to see him tonight
and tell him everything.
-He'll probably punch you in the face.
-I kind of hope he does.
Come on, Babe, snap out of it.
You really want to throw all this away
for a dipshit like that?
He's not a dipshit. He's a goodhearted guy
who we think is a weirdo...
...because he doesn't share
our sense of ironic detachment.
-All this hip, snide, smart-alecky--
-Bullshit?
Yes, bullshit.
Well, in a few moments,
I'll put on my Versace overcoat...
...get into my Mercedes,
drive to my Fifth Avenue apartment...
...and squeeze my girlfriend's big, fake boobs.
And that bullshit you're talking about
paid for all of it.
Good for you, Mac. But I'm still telling him.
Well....
Babe Bennett falls in love.
I'm happy for you. I am.
Gonna miss you, Babe.
Something fierce.
You think she'll like this?
All right.
Chicken parmesan? Terrific, thank you.
Let's hear it.
-She gonna like that, Mr. Deeds.
-Okay.
-Emilio, it looks beautiful.
-Thank you.
These roses might be a little too high.
I won't be able to see her.
-Do we have anything smaller?
-Yes, sir.
Okay.
Byron?
That's terrific.
-Would you mind sitting for a second?
-Yes, sir.
Say something to me. Pretend you're her.
-Me, sir?
-Please.
Well...
...it's nice of you to have invited me
to dine with you this evening.
It's my pleasure.
Actually, you're too tall. Can you slink down?
-Like this?
-That's good.
This is one of the best dates I've ever been on.
You make me feel very special.
You make me feel very special, too.
That's why I got this for you.
Okay, lean forward.
-I really like you a lot.
-I like you, too.
-I can't stop thinking about you.
Please let me touch your feet.
Okay, this is getting weird.
You can stand up now.
-Deeds!
-Fellows!
We wanted to come and wish you
the best on your big night.
Thanks a lot. I'm so nervous.
I never asked anybody to marry me before.
It's 7:30, time for lnside Access.
We're not in for any more
nasty surprises, are we?
I don't think so. I haven't done
anything stupid all day. I've been here.
Let's see what lame show they put on
when they don't have Deeds to pick on.
Excuse me!
-Could you put on Channel 8, please?
-You got it.
Welcome to lnside Access. I'm Mac McGrath.
All of us here at I. A. take pride
in our ability to handle...
...every story with sensitivity and empathy...
Okay, pal.
...while maintaining
an appropriate journalistic distance.
But what happens when a reporter
becomes part of what she's reporting?
What happens when a journalist
falls in love with an idiot?
That's Longfellow Deeds with Pam Dawson.
-I can't believe they involved her in this.
-A school nurse...
...who recently moved to New York City
from Winchestertonfieldville, lowa.
But wait. Doesn't Pam Dawson
bear a striking resemblance to...
...Babe Bennett,
a producer here at lnside Access?
In fact, the two are one and the same.
We'll wire your apartment
with state-of-the-art surveillance video.
Sounds good.
Deeds.
I came here to try to explain.
I'm the biggest sucker in the world.
This town can be brutal.
I don't belong here.
I can't run the company,
I can't even run my own life.
Sure you can.
The good news is the papers are ready.
Once you sign them, we'll get our stock
and you'll get your $40 billion.
I don't want that money. Just give it to a charity.
-What's a good charity?
-The United Negro College Fund?
Okay, give it to those guys.
Can we give you a ride to the airport?
The company chopper will take you home.
Thanks, anyway. I'll be all right on my own.
-Nice meeting you all.
-Nice meeting you, Deeds.
Goodbye!
Goodbye.
It's not right.
You must be Jan. My name is--
I know who you are. Wham-bam Dawson.
A. k. a. Little Miss Slut-Slut.
Okay, I deserve that.
Do you have any idea how much you hurt him?
You're not getting anywhere near that boy.
I have to find him and there's nothing
you can do to stop me.
-There's a lot I can do to stop you.
-He needs to know how bad I feel.
And that I would go to the end of the earth...
...I would do anything
to take back what I did to him.
I'm sorry, all I heard was,
"Blah, blah, I'm a dirty tramp."
Tell you what. You get by me...
...I'll tell you where he is.
Feeling crazy!
Come to Mama.
I was a rodeo clown for six years.
You'll have to step it up a notch, shorty.
You mean like this?
Where were you kicking?
I ain't got no balls, dummy!
Get up!
-Put me down!
-You got it!
-Just tell me where Deeds is.
-Bring your bony ass over here.
I want to cut you into eight slices of bitch-eroni.
Are you all right?
Good kick, honey. Good kick.
Crazy Eyes!
-All right.
-Here you go.
Peanut butter and gumballs. Nice combo.
Don't worry about what happened.
Time heals all things.
Except these crazy eyes.
It's good to be home. I know that much.
I wasn't talking to you, Deeds.
I was talking to that squirrel over there.
Although it's a shame about that Cedar fellow...
...tearing apart your uncle's company
and firing all those nice people.
Where'd you hear that?
I watch the stock market channel all the time.
I just watch because I suspect that anchorman
of being an evil leprechaun.
He can bullshit everybody else,
but he ain't fooling me.
There it is.
Someone!
Help!
Deeds! Help!
Oh, God! Deeds!
Oh, my God!
Where do you got the camera hidden,
in the woods?
No camera.
I'm so cold. Please!
You gonna get mugged in there, too?
I'm so...
...sorry.
I really love you.
Bullshit!
I'm coming!
Go down! Go down!
Here comes the black foot.
No!
I know it's gross, but grab it.
I got you. I got you.
-Oh, God, your foot is disgusting!
-I know, I know. Come here.
Come on, you okay? You okay?
I think so.
You didn't really fall out of an apple tree,
did you?
No.
But I really love you.
I don't even know who you are.
I'm sorry.
I am so sorry.
A company in tatters. Preston Blake's
great legacy gone to the highest bidder.
The shocking announcement from Chuck Cedar
today confirmed that Blake Media...
...will be stripped down
and sold off piece by piece.
The only man who could stand up
to Mr. Cedar and save the company...
...Longfellow Deeds, has apparently
given up his voting rights and left the city.
The sale's expected to pass
with unanimous consent...
...at the annual stockholders' meeting
here in New York tomorrow afternoon.
Sources indicate that virtually
all of Blake's 50,000 employees...
...are likely to lose their jobs.
Wait a minute. I'm a Blake employee.
Holy shit! This sucks.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the bottom line is that this divestiture...
...will result in every shareholder,
all of you and myself included...
...getting a substantial premium for our shares.
But before we vote, the company bylaws
require me to open the floor...
...to shareholders for statements
either for or against this buyout plan.
Does anyone wish to make a statement?
Dismantling this company
would be an insult to a great man.
You scared me.
It is an unspeakable outrage
and it cannot be allowed to happen.
Excuse me. I got a statement.
Longfellow Deeds.
Unfortunately, since you sold me
your 300 million shares...
-...you've no right to speak at this meeting.
-Unfortunately for you...
...I bought one share of Blake Media
this morning.
You told me every stockholder
has a say in this company.
Even the little guy.
You have two minutes, but remember,
I control 49 percent of this company.
You're gonna have to persuade
just about everyone else...
...to start hating money.
Hello, everybody. I'm Deeds.
For a little while, I was a big part of this company.
I was wicked rich and powerful.
Now being rich and powerful isn't a bad thing.
It looks like the Monopoly guy over there
is pretty darned psyched about it.
But the problem is
what can happen when you decide...
...that you would do absolutely anything
to become rich and powerful.
I don't know who licked the red off
your lollipop today...
...but you are preaching to the wrong choir.
All I'm saying is, when you were kids...
...did you dream
about becoming a savvy investor one day...
...who would think with his wallet
instead of his heart?
Come on, I know I didn't.
I wanted to be a fireman.
I wanted to be the guy everybody called on
if they were in trouble.
I wanted to help people...
...and yeah, I wanted to slide down
those wicked awesome poles.
But money,
that was the last thing I thought about.
What about you, sir?
Did you want to be a fireman?
No, I did not.
Truth be told, I wanted to be a veterinarian.
Cool. Why would you want to do that?
-I wanted to help sick animals.
-And what do you do now?
I own a chain of slaughterhouses.
You kind of went the other way
on that one, didn't you?
Okay.
In the back. Come on.
Tell me what you wanted to be.
I wanted to be a magician.
-And what do you do now?
-I operate a pornographic website.
That makes people happy also, I guess.
But kind of in a grosser way.
-Who else?
-I wanted to be a senator.
-I wanted to be a florist.
-International House Pancake.
I wanted to be a man.
That explains a lot.
I wanted to be a Ping-Pong champion.
But you're not those things
you wanted to be, are you?
Everybody made a compromise,
then another compromise, and now...
...you're about to put 50,000 people out of work,
to make a quick buck? Come on.
I bet if we ran into the 6th-grade versions
of ourselves right now...
...they would kick our asses
and put Bubble Yum in our hair...
...for even thinking about doing this.
He's right. I would've beat my greedy ass red.
I would've thrown myself off the merry-go-round.
I would've tied myself naked to a chair
and burned myself with lit cigarettes.
Did anyone here dream
of becoming a psychiatrist?
Just kidding, pal.
There's still hope for the kids inside of all of us.
Please don't break up my uncle's company.
I always wanted to do that.
Well...
...that was very touching, Deeds.
It appears this divestiture has been defeated.
Unless I'm forgetting something.
My 300 million votes...
...plus the five million votes I control
as proxy for the foreign investors.
So which way should I vote my 51 percent?
I vote aye.
305 million times.
The ayes have it. And Blake Media is no more.
Not so fast, Chuck.
Too bad for you, when I was a kid,
I wanted to be a good reporter.
Miss Bennett,
I wasn't aware you were a stockholder.
There's a couple things you're not aware of.
How to tweeze your eyebrows, for instance.
Also, when Deeds gave away his fortune,
he gave away something that wasn't his.
-What are you talking about?
-I have here the diary of Preston Blake.
I stole it and read it.
Please don't be mad at me.
I did it for good reasons, I promise.
I would like to read a passage
from Mr. Blake's diary...
...dated April 12, 1957.
"I am a volcano of lust.
"I've gotten this far in business
by following my heart.
"And I must follow it now...
"...in love.
"If she just gives me a sign, an opening."
Want me to wipe the leaves
on your ficus tree, Mr. Blake?
You can call me Preston.
Want me to wipe the leaves
on your ficus tree, Preston?
Yes.
Yes!
Who was this mystery woman?
I have here the Blake Media ledger
sign-in book from April, 1957.
On the night of the 12th, there was
only one woman working on Blake's floor.
Sadly, nine months later, she died,
giving birth to a son.
A son born...
...January 23, 1958.
That is my birthday.
To Miss Consuela Lopez.
That is my mother.
And the rightful heir to $40 billion!
That is my money?
A simple DNA test will show...
...that Emilio Lopez is the majority stockholder
to Blake Media.
-It is my money!
-That's your money!
That is my money!
Way to go, Emilio!
I will do good things for everyone.
Free flamenco lessons for all.
People, people! Please!
-That is my money.
-Don't be misled. These are all lies.
Mr. Cedar...
...you are fired.
You can't fire me!
I'm in control!
Get your hands off me! I'm Chuck Cedar!
At the lake, when you saved my life...
...which I never got a chance
to properly thank you for--
-You're welcome.
-You said you didn't know who I was.
And it made me realize I don't know who I am.
So I started working on it
and here's what I got so far.
My name is Babe Bennett.
I grew up in Syossett, Long lsland.
I have brown eyes and I don't know
what my natural hair color is anymore.
When I was in 5th grade,
I got a crush on Walter Cronkite.
And I really did have that Holly Hobby notebook
I was telling you about.
I love Bruce Springsteen, Almond Roca
and Abbott and Costello movies.
I don't like licorice or my ankles.
More importantly,
I know that I messed up real bad.
And I'd be willing to spend the rest of my life...
...begging you to give me another chance...
...because I am so deeply in love with you...
...and I know it's definitely
that forever kind of love--
You're crazy.
You have beautiful ankles.
Let's go home.
You're fired! You! You!
Oh, you, sir. You are definitely fired.
I'd like to stay. I think I can really do
some good if I just got another chance.
Not fired. But tomorrow morning,
you let me change your socks.
Okay.
And you, Long-Long-Longfellow...
...you are the one who made all this possible...
...with your beautiful words
and your beautiful spirit.
And Miss Bennett, with her beautiful research.
How can I thank you?
All I want is your friendship, Emilio.
You're a good man.
I'll miss you.
Deeds!
-How about $1 billion?
-All right.
Done.
Holy Jeez!
I can't believe it!
-What's that?
-A letter from Hallmark.
They're actually going to buy one of my cards.
-My gosh! Which one?
-The one I wrote for you, remember it?
Do I remember?
"Hard to breathe, feels like floating
"So full of love my heart's exploding
"Mouth is dry, hands are shaking
"My heart is yours for the taking
"Acting weird, not myself
"Dancing around like the Keebler elf
"Finally time for this poor schlub
"to know how it feels to fall in lub"
I'm so proud of you!
Can you believe Deeds bought us all these?
Damn, these things are fast!
I'm okay!
Subtitle Revised by HchC
字幕翻译: Lvs
Translated By Lvs
发行网站: http://unity.starwcn.net
=====老鹰出品[Glede]======
Hello, 山下的伙计们
我离珠峰峰顶只有不到100码了
但说实在的,这样的假期实在太闷了...
...还不如回去工作来得刺激些
先生,您不再考虑一下吗?
毕竟,您已经82岁了
我82岁?
这些数字对我毫无意义,
我的冒险才开始
先生! 先生!
- 暴风雪正在增强
- 情况非常危险
我们必须马上下山
可峰顶就在眼前,小子
我要下山了,你最也好下去
好吧,随便你
星期一开会再见,我会带上炸甜圈
这悲惨的画面今天一直出现在我们面前
Preston Blake，这位可敬的梦想家,
从拥有一家电台变成当今世界的传媒巨子
...离我们而去了,享年82岁.
稍后有详细报道
您正收看的是Blake新闻网络
Blake媒体公司--即本新闻网络的父公司,
...受Blake去世消息的影响,
其股票今早大幅下跌...
...在Blake的2号人物--Chuck Cedar
发表声明后,股价有所反弹
就算华佗在世...
...Preston Blake也不能死而复生
据闻，Blake单身一人,
无儿无女，也未定下遗嘱
那么，谁将会继承公司百分之49的股份...
...也就是400亿美元呢?
我们将与Blake先生周围的每个人接触
包括他的理发师...
...敬请收看明天的"深入追击"
别错过, 我是Mac McGrath.
- 拍好没有?
- 拍好了!
Babe? Babe在哪儿?
- 我不会放过你的!
- Babe!
我要挂电话了
不值一提的理发师!
你就这么点儿本事?
人们通常会和自己理发师聊很多事
他们是20多年的好朋友
我不会让这家伙上节目,
你最好给我找点更好的东西，要快
不然你就有麻烦了
继承人找到没有?
马上就会有消息传真过来
我正在叫人调查...
...全国各地的出生记录,包括波多黎各和关岛
我们还开了一个小小的赌局,
关岛的赔率是1000比1
你觉得很好玩,是吧?
一个简单的血缘关系将会决定公司的命运
我不是这个意思,这的确很让人烦恼
烦恼? 你满脸的胡子可以叫烦恼
你的破烟斗,还有你的一口黄牙都可以叫烦恼
而如果我失去了公司,那就会是"灭顶之灾"
有谁认识 Mendlesohn医生?
恭喜你,你得了结肠痉挛
原来如此
"Longfellow Deeds."
Chuck,我们应该到了
老天啊,简直是一片野地
瞧啊, 左侧有敌机!
来啊,把它打下来!
你们俩迷路了么?
我们在找Longfellow Deeds先生
那是Deeds的名字吗?
如果你指的是那位Longfellow Deeds先生...
...是的,那是他的名字
我可不知道Deeds的名字,我还以为是Greg呢
- 也许是Longfellow.
- 也许吧
我不清楚,不过我知道有个家伙的名字叫Greg,
要不要我去叫他?
不用了,谢谢
告诉我们Deeds先生住哪儿行么?
好吧,好吧,别着急!
我带你们去
请进吧,伙计们
- 他住批萨饼店?
- 谁会住在批萨饼店里呢！
他住在楼上, 这店是他开的
劳驾请问，Deeds先生在么?
抱歉,他出去送货了,送货的家伙病了
- 你看起来不象有病啊, Murph.
- 哎呀,我忘了自己在装病
- 你们俩想把我骗回来,是吧
- Murph, 穿上围裙过来帮忙
你们合起来耍我,对吧?
那么, Deeds太太在么?
Deeds 太太?
我看那小子连约会还没试过呢!
- 那他什么时候回来?
- 一定在吃完午饭前,今天是"卡片日"
- 卡片日?
- Deeds 经常会写一些贺卡
每个星期一, 他会读给大家听,
然后挑一张...
...寄给贺卡公司
虽然目前，他还没能卖出一张，但...
...将来一定会的
要来点什么?
"亲爱的：
"我爱你，全心全意"
"我和你,就象面包奶油不分离"
有意思
喜欢吗,先生们?
Hallmark贺卡公司觉得很不错,
很有发展潜力
- 你是Longfellow Deeds吗?
- 叫Deeds就行, 朋友
别叫Longfellow什么的那么麻烦
我是Chuck Cedar, Blake媒体公司的执行总载
这位是Cecil Anderson, 法律主管
握手太见外了,我们流行拥抱
你好吗, 欢迎来本镇
来吧,别不好意思
胡子很漂亮,象林肯似的
请坐吧,兄弟们
- Murph!
- Deeds?
- 你不是病了么?
- 我骗你的,朋友
你玩我啊?
- 是么?
- 是的
-  Deeds先生?
-  叫Deeds就行
听你电话里的声音好象病的很重,
好小子, 再说一遍听听
Deeds, 我今天喉咙发炎没法上班了
难以置信,你完全可以去演广播剧什么的
- 多谢,朋友
- Sure.
Hey, Deeds. 快点读贺卡吧,
我还要回去值勤
我得去了,很高兴见到两位
Deeds先生, "Preston Blake"这个名字你熟悉吗?
我妈界婚后姓 Blake
这星期只读一张,但我预感它会是一个转折点
Preston Blake 是你母亲的叔叔
你不是开玩笑吧,我有个叔公?
真意外,他好么?
他死了
噢,真可惜,我有什么能帮忙的....
Deeds! Deeds!
等等,伙计们
Blake死后留给你一大笔遗产
一共是...
...400亿美圆! 全是你的, Deeds.
等会儿
你刚才说什么? "我还要回去值勤"
你又不是警察!
没错,警服是我买的
扮扮警察有什么大不了的,哈哈!
不知死活的家伙!
好吧,各位观众,表演开始
这是一张"结婚50周年卡"
如今那可真的很难得
"50年风风雨雨"
"可曾记得,当年动物园中携手同游
"把酒言欢"
干杯!
"愿多陪你50载"
"哪怕老婆变肥婆"
太绝了! 他怎么想出来的?
你以后不用再送批萨了, Deeds.
你现在富可敌国
那和送批萨有什么关系?
女士们! 上面那盒是你们的
-谢谢你, Deeds.
-当然
-真好吃!
-Deeds, 有什么新鲜事?
我刚知道自己有个叔公,不过他死了
太遗憾了
-但他留给我400亿美圆
-那是件好事
Oh, 是啊!
别把钱全花在那些录音机上
我不会的
这些是你朋友, Deeds?
抱歉,Chuck, Cecil,
她们是Jane, Kitty and Sue.
-很高兴见到你, Cecil.
-是我的荣幸, Kitty(小猫)
还是叫你 "喵"
别发情了, Anderson.
-这笔钱怎么会由我继承呢?
-你是Blake先生目前最近的亲戚了
- 是吗? 没其他人了么?
- 没有,事实如此
老天,我甚至没见过他!
帮我拿一下好么?
Wetherley先生,你好吗?
很好, Deeds. 正想去一趟药房
好的,我帮你走快两步吧!
- 你太太好么?
- 她很好
- 好极了,替我问候她
- 我会的
到了
- 谢谢你背我, Deeds.
- 别客气
我们想请你去纽约,就几天时间
要请你签几份文件
什么文件?
实际上,你已经继承了Blake媒体公司的
300万股份
Chuck和我, 还有其他股东, 将会用...
...400亿美圆购买你的股份,
为此我们必须到处贷款--
别提那些金融方面的麻烦事了!
我们需要一些时间来玩文字游戏罢了
这段时间,我们希望你能够避开新闻界
几星期后,此事会慢慢被遗忘....
你也不想这个小镇被记者们糟蹋,对吧?
Oh, 当然不!
- 鬼眼!
- 什么?
你好吗,朋友?
你要的批萨,是你最喜欢的口味
Oh, 太好了!
法国风味外加巧克力夹心饼, Deeds.
你犯了什么事儿?
因为袭击邮差,监禁一晚
那家伙想给我下咒, 就象巫师之类
- 你肯定?
- 不,或许他只是在招手?
- 他们是谁?
- 这是纽约来的Chuck 和Cecil
我不喜欢他们
好吧,很高兴见到你
我从没去过纽约,可以去看看风景
- 给我一小时准备一下,好么?
- 没问题
我可能是自从Jimmy McNally去过迪斯尼后,
第一个离开本镇的人
过几天再见, 各位!
明天是儿童免费日,别忘了把凳子弄干净
别担心,我会打理好一切的
- 去吧,玩个痛快!
- 我会想你的
再见,Jan. 再见, Murph.
- 来张卡片吧!
- 对!
"当我踏上旅途进城去"
"从未离开过故乡,一个乡巴佬?
"当我离去,会惦记大家"
"衣锦还乡时别忘了带上礼物"
没问题, pal!
别乱跑
发生了本年度最轰动的事件,
但我们竟然一无所获?
你们想去当个小报记者吗? 我不这么看!
为了新闻,你们必须不择手段
想当初...
...我躲在雪糕箱子里
- ...在Tom和Roseanne的垃圾箱里足足呆了两天
- 有消息了!
我在Blake公司的消息人士说
公司的直升机...
... 今天中午起程飞往Mandrake山谷
-...有两名乘客
- 去哪儿?
新汉普郡的一个乡下小镇
但回来时有三名乘客
- 多了一个人!
- 聪明!
干的好, Marty，第三个乘客就是我们要找的人
他们本应5点钟到达
但他们在康涅狄格临时停留了一阵
能吃到这么好的东西真是太棒了！
谢谢你们，实在是太美味了
- 乐意效劳
- 觉得味道怎么样, Cecil?
你胡子上沾了点东西，哈哈，骗你的
瞧他多有意思！
两小时内节目就要开始
到那时，我要知道他的一切
听见了吗, Jim.
还有, Babe. Babe?
Babe死到哪儿去了?
你又没去开会，Mac发火了
等我把Blake的消息给他，他就会消气的
- 你有什么消息?
- 没有，你呢?
我很快就会有大把消息了
你得帮帮我
我需要这个新闻，
我身无分文，而Mac还要炒了我
你会身无分文?
这儿就数你赚的最多了！
- 你的钱都花哪儿去了?
- 买鞋
明天中午我会把消息全告诉你
...这次别让你那个开CLUB的男朋友...
...再用摩托车撞我了
别担心，我们最近没怎么来往
是吗? 你们分手了?
Babe, 干嘛睡在这儿? 我那儿有空房间
我去过你那儿,记得吗?
我睡醒时发现, 你喘着粗气站我床边
我那是哮喘发作,找不到药
嘿,慢点, 伙计们
你们在打饱嗝啊!
喜欢足球么? 帕特队今年可能夺得联合会杯
海豚队没那么强,至于喷气机队只配掂底
如果我是你,我可不会这么说, Deeds先生
- 叫我Deeds就行. 你说为什么?
- 你是喷气机队的老板, Deeds.
是吗?
那可真没面子
希望他们可别在总决赛碰上帕特队,
要不然,我宁愿去死好过些
我还是觉得有点担心
你不是刚抽完大麻吧?
你担心什么呢!
- 这小子简直是上天的恩赐
- 要是他不肯卖股份怎么办?
我既然能说服整个公司...
...自然也能摆平这小子!
你看他!
不错, Anderson.
够了!
真扫兴
老天爷!
你好吗, 纽约?
我来啦!世界上最棒的城市!
恭喜你, Deeds, 你现在是全纽约最
有钱的单身汉了!
我可不想别人因为我有钱而追求我
话虽如此, 但你去我们的俱乐部看看之后
或许就不会这么想了
是吗?
我爸救过我妈的命
她当时滑冰掉进冰窟窿里
我常想,我可能也得这样,够刺激的
看来,我要经常帮你留意
那些遇到麻烦的女士才行
- 那太好了
- 喂! Mandrake山谷来的 !
保安,抓住他!
站住! 别跑!
那张照片能值十万块,
而且不用一小时就会满天飞了
他这套惊险动作也值这个价钱了
不,他该被割断喉咙,无耻的家伙,
来吧,咱们走
这就是我叔公的家?
是的, 他在这儿住了35年
- 你像是突然冒出来似的
- 我非常非常的敏捷, 先生
我见识过了，我叫Deeds.
我是Emilio, 先生，我是您的仆人
仆人？ 我可用不着什么仆人,
交个朋友倒是可以
朋友?
没错,好朋友
您想回房间去吗? 今天一定很劳累了吧
- 你的意思呢, Chuck?
- 那里很安全
我们可能要花几天时间
来准备文件让你签字
- 在自己家里慢慢享受吧
- 妙极了
- 回头见
- 先生,我们一会儿见
好的,幸会了,我是Deeds
- 我是Reuben, 先生
- 这电梯真是不错
看好他, Emilio. 否则有你好瞧的
见到您我很高兴,先生
这份工作怎么样, Reuben?
"有起有落"!
没错! 没错!
说的好!
好家伙, 你怎么这么快啊?
身手敏捷, 先生, 这边走
Wow.
怎么了,先生?
- 是回声,先生
- 是啊,你试试
- 我,先生?
- 很有意思的
来吧,大声点儿
- 厉害
- 谢谢你,先生
嘿,朋友,想不想试试?
不错
大家都想试试吗 ? 一起怪叫
真有意思, 不过我有点累了,想去睡觉
- 这边
- 谢谢你们, 大家去睡个好觉
晚安
你是不是打算睡在那儿,直到邮报把新闻全抢走?
你好吗, 纽约?
屋里竟然有个饮水器,不错!
是夏威夷果汁
他喜欢...
...夏威夷果汁
Wow! 又被你吓了一跳!
恐怕您还没适应我的敏捷
可能吧,你在那儿干什么?
我帮您换袜子
帮我换袜子? 不必了,起来吧
谢谢您
而且,你一定不会想碰我的右脚
我当童子军时,右脚严重冻伤,
你瞧
够恐怖的,是吧?
一想起它,恐怕我这一辈子都会作恶梦
是的,有人也这么说过
真正恐怖的是, 这只脚一点感觉都没有!
你就算用力踩,我也不会疼
- 来,试试踩两脚
- 还是不必了吧,先生
踩吧, 求你了
没感觉
你就这么大劲儿? 不如去壁炉那儿
把烧火棍拿来, 给我来几下结实的
- 一定要这么做吗?
- 多有意思啊,去拿吧
我的朋友有空时都喜欢这么干
来吧
来呀, 狠狠来几下
- 没事儿
- 真的?
恐怖吧?
完全没感觉, 真变态, 接着打
没事儿
开始觉得过瘾了,对吧?
来呀! 别手下留情!
没错,就是这样!
啊！你这个变态的家伙！
你真狠啊!
我骗你的,朋友
- 真被你吓着了
- 我看见了,你的样子....
我要去问问Cedar和Anderson
今天该干什么呢?
帮我把它拔出来好么, 我给钉在地上了
行了
我必须强调, 这次的会谈请各位保守秘密...
...直到我正式获得Blake先生的全部股份
如果那些内容可以接受的话,
在我看来...
...2000个电台已经是诸位的了
早上好
Deeds.
大家在忙什么?
一点生意上的事
这间房子也有回音, 你们一定知道
你有何贵干?
只是来看看今天有什么事可干
所有的事情都有人负责
总有点什么事吧? 在没签文件之前
这里还是属于我的,对吧?
什么?
请各位稍等片刻
当然
你好吗, 老兄? 我昨晚一直梦见冰天雪地, 你呢?
我也一直在做梦,可是和你的不一样
Deeds.
公司每个股东,无论大小,都有发言权
但那是在每年的股东大会上
其他的时间, 公司的运作是由行政人员
- 比如我,来负责管理的
- 你的意思是我不应该插手
是的,而且这也不是什么有意思的事
公司有太多的事情要处理...
...完全是24个小时工作制
我昨晚只睡了三个小时
那应该是"21个小时工作制",对吧?
让开,小姐,
我才不管他妈的什么会议!
Cedar先生, 对不起--
上个赛季我打了3500码, 现在我不干了
除非你们这帮有钱的混蛋
同意新的和约
伙计,当着女士的面,说话要小心些
你闭上嘴,有钱的臭小子!
马上给我加工资,否则你们这帮混--
我警告过你的
说真的,你倒下去的样子活象一袋番茄,
来吧
起来吧,大块头
女士们先生们,足球!
你的合同是怎么回事?
我认为如果我打的好,就应该签新的和约,
赚更多的钱!
如果你打的不好,
我们能不能重新签约减少你的酬金呢?
妈的, 休想!
我是说, 不行
这对我可不公平
- 他是我们的得分手
- 我明白, Chuck. 让我处理吧
听着,朋友们,我要提高工资...
...否则我一场都不打了
好吧, 我们只能请你走人了!
-"请我走人"?
- 没错,你被解雇了
那么我可以与其他球队签约了?
随便你,不过我建议你改变一下态度...
...否则,没人会愿意和你共事的
再见
Deeds.
Kevin 两年前得了Heisman奖,
他是我们的顶尖球员
- 别担心,他会回来的
- 你们会后悔的!
这东西真不错
干嘛不出去走走, 去看看纽约,
好东西还多着呢, 带上这个
还是留在这儿吧, 好吧, 有事尽管叫我
- 当然
- 谢谢, 再见 Anderson.
另外, 各位好像是法国人,
[法语]大家好!
你染金发可真性感
样子变化不大么？希望没人认得出我
我喜欢你这个样子，不过还是让我去吧，
可能有危险的
他喜欢的是落难女子，不是浑身香水味的男人
- 他来了
- 谢谢你带我出来
- 别客气
- 快打开摄像机,动手吧
- 快点啊,你得袭击我!
- 好吧!
- 天哪,救命!
- 来吧
- 救命,抢劫啊!
- 好啊!
救命! 救命! 打劫啊!
- 够了!
- 祝你好运,回头办公室见
- 别担心,我会抓住他的
- 噢,老天!
站住
给我趴下!
兄弟,你是怎么搞的?
起来
小姐,手袋帮你拿回来了,
老兄,找份正经工作吧
小姐! 小姐!
- 你没事吧?
- 怎么回事?
我扶你起来
没事了,没事了
小姐你刚刚被纽约歹徒袭击
我猜,那只不过是个小毛贼罢了
竟然还满身香水味
- 我帮你把提包拿回来了
- 谢谢
- 要不要送你去医院?
- 不,不必了
我没事儿,只是有些头晕和受惊过度
我没事的
别这样,你还是去医院看看吧
我真的没事,我只是...
...或者走走就行了....
- 能扶我一下么?
- 没问题
谢谢你
非常感谢
我叫Pam. Pam Dawson.
我叫Deeds. 我不是本地人,来这儿旅游
你从哪来?
Mandrake山谷, 一个没多少人知道的小镇
在新安普郡
我也是从小镇来的
- 在爱荷华
- 是吗? 在哪儿?
Winchestertonfieldville
爱荷华州Winchestertonfieldville,一个小镇
对不起
- 你来纽约干什么?
- 我在学校当护士
- 你不可能是护士
- 为什么,你不相信吗?
你这么好心,怎么可能是护士
我学校的护士可恶极了,
每次我告诉她我胃疼...
...她都会把我赶回教室,
命令我"不许哭哭啼啼"的!
- 真是太可怕了!
- 是啊,我天天都这么说!
我很想念自己的妈妈
多可爱!
Dawson小姐?
我在想,你是否愿意与我...
...共进一个纽约式的晚餐?
天哪！
听起来很不错
- 是吗?
- 是的
- 那咱们去吧
- 好吧
去死吧，混蛋
这么说你自己开了间批萨店，还喜欢写诗
你来这儿只是为旅游?
事实上，我刚刚继承了400亿美元遗产
那可真不少, 但我总觉得那么大一笔钱
多少有些来路不正
有道理
你的金发真漂亮
我有瑞典学童
- 是吗?
- 是
我祖父住在ABBA.
ABBA乐队?
劳驾, 有没有什么名人来这儿?
什么大人物都有
是吗? 我们那儿可没什么名人
有一次,史蒂芬.金 路过我们的加油站...
...但是竟然没人敢和他搭话
我想他一定很可怕
加油站的员工Jake, 和他对望过一眼
当晚体重就掉了200磅
Wow.
你们的奶酪烤鸡很快就好了
好的,伙计 , 我看到
那边有一对夫妇在庆祝结婚周年
把这个给他们,但别说是我们给的
这差不多有2万快呢!
就跟他们说,是餐厅酬宾活动之类的
谢了,伙计
这可是个花钱的好办法
- 我不会认错人吧?
- 谁?
Preston Blake的侄子, 身价400亿的那个
我们得会会他, Dave?
是吗, 那个歹徒没什么事儿就好
- Deeds先生
- 什么事?
Simonds先生想请您赏脸过去坐坐!
为什么?
因为大家想一睹您女朋友的风采
是吗, 他可真有眼光
真是个热情的拥抱, Deeds.
非常感谢你的邀请, 我们非常高兴
- 我们在哪儿见过面吗?
- 我想没有,除非你的孩子生过病
您现在是城里的大人物了,Deeds先生
这我可不知道
我在Metropolitan歌剧院工作...
...我们百分之五十以上的经费
是由Blake媒体公司提供的
因此,我代表歌剧院:
"感-谢-你"
唱得真好!
不过你该感谢我叔公,而不是我
他是个有趣的人
我和他在古根海姆委员会共事过
是吗? 我可没听说过那个地方,
不过祝它好运
我很乐意为你在"纽约人"写篇文章
"纽约人"是什么?
是一份杂志
发表一些短评和讽刺漫画
我经常看Mandrake的小报,
他们也登很多漫画
知道最有意思的是谁吗, 那个叫贝利的家伙
整天戴着顶帽子,到处惹事
很荣幸见到了一位真正的作家, George.
我一直也想发表点东西...
... 但Hallmark的门槛实在太高了
- Hallmark?
- 他喜欢写贺卡
- 试试而已
- 您一定要让我们见识一下
- 我喜欢你的口音, "法国先生"
- 谁是"法国先生"?
- 他象不像那个"法国先生"?
- 完全没听说过
来嘛
好吧,就读一个吧
这是我最近在写的一张母亲节贺卡
"老妈, 是你带我来到这个星球"
"生我时你痛苦了14个钟头"
"每次玩耍后,您把汽水送到我手中"
"我爱你,妈,愿您母亲节乐也融融"
就是这样了
- 了不起的即兴创作!
-"天才,天才,天才"
你平时是用蜡笔写诗的吧?
有意思!
我知道你们为什么请我们过来了,
想拿我寻开心,对吧?
- 别当真, Deeds.
- 闭嘴, George.
对你们来说,我也许很可笑,
但如果你们到Mandrake去...
...可笑的会是你们,
但是却没人会嘲笑你们...
...令你们尴尬,
因为那不是待客之道!
也许我写的东西不怎么样,
但有些人很喜欢
不管怎么说,我尽力了,
我们要走了
对不起,Pam.
希望你别在意!
要不是Dawson 小姐在这儿,
我会好好收拾你们的
我不介意
那好吧
"不"
我好像拉裤子了
咱们去哪儿看风景?
我先去补一补妆
好的,我帮你拿外套
伙计们,这两万块算是赔偿你们的损失,
非常抱歉!
- 幸会了,各位
- 谢谢
上帝, 千载难逢的机会
Mac,我要加薪
喂,兄弟,你好吗?
老天爷啊, 你是John McEnroe(前网球明星)!
我看见你收拾那帮无礼的家伙,干得好!
有时候真是忍无可忍, 你明白的,对吧
Johnny Mac?
- 我明白
- 我叫Deeds
Deeds, 幸会了
去和我喝两杯吧
Dawson小姐, 这位是John McEnroe.
- Dawson小姐, 很高兴见到你
- 我也是
我答应陪Dawson小姐去观光
这里风景不错,我很喜欢
我带你们看看纽约不为人知的一面
- 你认为怎么样, Dawson小姐?
- 听起来挺有意思的!
为狂欢之夜干杯!
发生什么事?
吃几片阿司匹林吧, Deeds先生
就不会那么头疼了
- 我怎么换上睡衣了?
- 我帮您换的
我很小心的,先生
我猜,全曼哈顿的酒昨晚都让我喝光了!
Dawson小姐也是这么说的
Dawson小姐! 我记得好像没送她回家, 她好吗?
我自己拿主意,用公司的车送她回去了
她遇到麻烦,我帮了她
昨晚,我梦见她了
通常, 喝醉的人是不会做梦的
书上说的
什么事儿, Chuck?
美国最新的亿万富翁...
-...愚蠢的酒鬼
- 这是什么?
昨晚, Longfellow Deeds一定很尽兴
他们现在知道我叫Longfellow了
殴打完几位社会名流之后...
Deeds 又和"网球坏孩子" -- John McEnroe
混到了一块儿!
多么愚蠢的行径!
他们是怎么拍到的?
小心,Johnny!
你怎么开车的!
不知羞耻的家伙!
不,先生. 你才不知羞耻!
- 太过瘾了, 兄弟!
- Johnny McEnroe!
瞧啊, Deeds和McEnroe在一起!
太厉害了!
是啊，我也很喜欢"沙滩小子"
你这种表现可不是我们现在所需要的
什么意思?
目前来说,你是我们最大的股东...
...你的这种行为...
...将会直接影响公司的稳定
是我的错
是我的错,是我的错
好了,好了
- 是我的错
- 没事的
需要我帮您叫车去葬礼吗 ? Cedar先生
什么葬礼?
你叔公的
- 是今天?
- 是的
我去穿衣服
- 听着,多嘴的东西
- 先生?
那个白痴一回到乡下...
你这个波多黎各笨蛋也给我滚！
我来自西班牙,先生
Ol?
"此刻, Preston弟兄必在天际飞翔"
"只因,一生爱心不停释放"
"他如今高高在上..."
"...无人会将他遗忘"
"伟大的生命匆匆逝去..."
"未完的事业何人承继"
这位老兄写贺卡肯定能发大财!
"我们的朋友Preston Blake..."
信念坚定,无人能移!
胆识超群,无人能敌!
品格优良,无人能比!
上帝保佑,愿他安息!
阿门
请留步, 牧师, 您说的太精彩了
"在天际翱翔"那段简直太感人了
- 谢谢你,兄弟
- 我生日那天,朋友们送了个啤酒杯给我
上面写着 "未能展翅高飞,只因鹤立鸡群"
但还是你的诗更好
都很好
安息吧, Preston.
让我们结束今天的仪式
我还想说两句
Deeds的口才是学校里最好的
Deeds?
只是顺便说几句,阁下
我们不是在看"史酷比"吗 ?
Hi, 我是 Deeds.
Preston Blake是我的叔公
在来这儿的路上, 我做了一首诗献给他
请允许我为大家朗诵
当然,它和Sharpton牧师的大作无法相比
但我还是想和大家分享
"你攀登高山,建造大楼"
"创办报纸,还有精彩的TV-SHOW"
"摆弄股票,你最拿手"
"你喜欢,有仆人侍侯左右"
"可惜未能与你相处, 哪怕一分一秒"
"不然,日子该有多美好"
不错,很压韵
"我去世时,您不该把泪掉"
"因为你我在天堂相会"
"多么美妙,多么美妙!"
写得不错!
Amen.
或许是你们的习俗,但在我们那儿
...一般会打开棺材,以便大家能看见遗体,
追思凭吊...
抱歉各位,我看还是盖上吧!
他还冻得硬邦邦的
差不多了
我会帮你照料公司的, 我爱你
很高兴见到你,多谢你的大房子
真疯狂
各位走好!
嘿! 这家伙真是古怪
- 你自己小心点
- 今晚约了他 ?
是的,我4点钟给他打电话,
然后就准备开工
别忘了, 我是Pam Dawson, 纯洁的少女,
来自Winchestertonfieldville的护士小姐
真有你的!
你,纯洁? 哈哈哈 !
- 好的,谢谢你
- 先生,你这是 ?
- 是我让他拿的
- 多谢了,Deeds.
别客气,伙计. 幸会了
随时欢迎你来用洗手间,知道吗?
- 好的,Deeds.!
今天葬礼上我的表现怎么样?
你的话很感人,先生
我还是有些过意不去
我把叔公的胳膊给掰断了
还好,他已经死了, 先生.
很奇怪,即使他的脸冻成那个样子...
...可我觉得他还是很快乐,对不对?
- 他是这样的
- 来,陪我坐坐
他天天都是这样...
...我们相处了差不多30年
你们都聊些什么话题?
人生,爱情,艺术,生意之类的
他令我获益良多
- 你一定很怀念他
- 是的
他就像我父亲一样
你知道的,我没见过自己的父亲,而母亲...
我刚出生她就去世了
- 想来点可可豆么?
- 不了,谢谢
我还有很多活要干
- 谢谢你,不用了
- 慢慢吃
还有一件事
你叔公也没让我给它换袜子
我喜欢脚
不知为什么!
喂?
你好,是Deeds么? 我是Pam, Pam Dawson.
你能来电话太好了! 昨晚的事我非常抱歉
我不常喝酒
你酒量不错嘛
可惜还是吐了你一身!
别在意,反正那条裙子我也不是太喜欢
又有一个电话进来,
能麻烦你等一等吗?
- 没问题
- 谢谢
喂
Deeds先生, 我是Kevin Ward,
就是上次你揍的那个四分卫
噢,我想起来了,什么事儿,朋友?
我反覆考虑过了,我不该那样目中无人,
我希望能帮您赢得超级杯
- 那太好了,伙计
- 我爸想和您说两句
Deeds. 我是Buddy Ward, Kevin的父亲
你好吗, Ward先生?
我想感谢你给我儿子上了一课
他是个好孩子,只是
在女士面前说话时要文明一些
我会提醒Kevin,是谁生他出来的
那太好了
你在女士面前说脏话?
别打我,爸,别打我!
Pam
我听着呢
你在干什么呢,上班?
- 是的, 我现在在医疗室
- 有"顾客"吗?
顾客? 噢,你是说生病的孩子
恩, 小Billy在这儿
- 你哪儿不舒服, Billy?
- Dawson小姐, 我肚子疼
你可以试试安静的躺一会儿
你干得不错
我拉屎屎了
臭死了
看来你要忙一阵子了...
...我还是直说了吧
我今晚想约你出来,你愿意吗?
我很愿意
太好了
不过不能去喝酒, 免得给公司惹麻烦
好的, 从小家里人就教育我不要喝酒
连酒心糖也别吃
没错, 咱们去干点别的吧
今晚见
好的,再见
我得试试这个
有意思吧?
上垒还是出局?
明白!
这是什么? 我叔公的日记!
- 我能看么?
- 自家人
没错,自家人,没问题
好吧,晚安! 我后背疼死了!
- 很高兴和你们交易
- 谢谢你,Deeds先生
谢谢你们的自行车
这两万块你打算怎么花?
买冰激凌.
你呢?
退学
好主意,傻瓜才去上学,你们看看我!
这公园真美
这些树有没有让你想起Winchestertonfieldville?
是啊,当然,我想起了很多
在那里的生活很有意思吧?
非常有意思
我还记得那时到街角的杂货铺...
...买麦芽糖奶昔
你家的房子什么样?
很大,维多利亚式的
在大街的右边
- 蓝色的百叶窗, 大门是红色的
- 真不错
- 屋前的院子里有一架秋千
- 太可爱了
记得那次我从老Radley的苹果树上摔下来...
...把胳膊给摔断了
我父亲, 那时他还没有...
死于麻风病
...他抱起我,一直跑到Pepper大夫家
Pepper大夫
是的
还好有他
- 想坐一会儿吗?
- 好的
- 谢谢你
- 乐意效劳
在来的路上,我一直在读叔公的日记
他9岁时写道...
他们是唯一有收音机的家庭...
...他梦想将来能成为一名DJ(音乐主持人)
DJ?
知道吗,我小时候一直梦想能成为记者
经常到处去采访别人...
...然后在自己的小本子上写呀、写呀
弄得别人很讨厌，结果捱了不少揍
- 还记得打你的家伙吗?
- 忘了,那是很久以前了
但我奶奶却对我说:
"总有一天你会成为大记者...
"...改变这个世界"
你每天都在改变着这个世界, 你是孩子们的好护士
对了,还有一件事是关于我叔公的
在他晚年那段日子, 他会每天早上3点钟...
到自己的电台, 做一个小时的DJ
太有意思了
所以,别放弃自己的愿望,
你会成为记者的
只要你不放弃
是那样就好了
- 不好,着火了!
- 着火?
- 我们得去帮忙
- 我们?
- 咱们走
- 去着火那里?
- Fifi, 到这儿来
- 跳啊,我们会接住你的
走开, 我不能丢下我的小猫,
它们是我唯一的亲人
她发疯了!
- 噢,小乖乖,你们在哪儿?
- 上去,快!
我是Longfellow Deeds, Mandrake镇的
义务消防局长. 我这就上去!
- 他发疯了
- 竟然要上去!
- 小心,伙计!
- 他要干什么?
瞧啊!
- Sully, 那个家伙是谁?
- 我不知道
他说他是Mandrake消防局的
- 老天,这是什么功夫啊?
- 简直是人猿泰山的亲戚
和纽约最勇敢的人并肩战斗
是我的荣幸!
小心!
- 我来救你了
- 小乖乖,你们在哪啊?
- 女士!
- 老天,太热了
- 小猫咪,到妈妈这儿来
- 请别慌,会没事儿的
好吧, 但我决不会丢下我的猫
- 一共几只?
- 7只.
真他妈的多, 快开始找吧!
- 抱歉说粗话
- 接受你的道歉
- 火灾让我兴奋
- 别客气,尽情享受!
- 过来
- 那个是Freddy.
- 下去吧!
- 不,我的孩子!
- 接的好, Pam!
- 你扔的也不错, Deeds!
- 那是Frobo. 谢谢你
- 来了,伙计们
让我来!
- 还有几只呢
- Okay, okay.
老天爷, 一只猫!
好一个长传. 我来了,猫咪
接的漂亮!
还有一只
Fifi, 你在哪儿?
- 我找到Fifi了
- Oh, 太好了!
坚持住,小兄弟!
我来,我来!
来吧,咱们一起跳
小心啊!
别担心,这对他们是小菜一碟
Oh,天哪!
Deeds.
我没事
你没事吧?
是的,太谢谢你了!
救命啊!
Longfellow Deeds又在生事了
Coretta Keeling女士成了他受害者...
...她非常爱自己的小猫咪
不幸,被Deeds知道了
- 我来了!
- 走开!
- 真绝了
- 两个一起来!
- 杀害猫咪的凶手!
- 害死了可爱的猫咪之后...
...他又把手伸向了Keeling小姐
上帝!
我拍的不是这样
这位Longfellow受到任何惩罚了吗? 没有!
当然不会!
我们所遵守的法律在这些公子哥儿眼中,
只是一个玩笑罢了
这就是Longfellow Deeds---本周最愚蠢的傻瓜
到底是谁? 是谁编辑了带子
是我, 你做的那个版本非常好,
但我需要更夸张一点
事实上那是一个多好的素材啊!
他救了那个女人和她的7只小猫
- 他是个英雄!
- 英雄是不错
- 但堕落和疯狂更有观众
这片子是你拍的,干得好,
继续努力!
天哪,我们怎么能这样对一个好人?
好人? 好人?
瞧瞧我!
他暴揍我那时,像个好人吗?
- 可你是歹徒啊!
- Babe!
相信我,世界上没有那么好的人!
别傻了!
不该这么对他的
他也不该得到你!
我的脖子!
他们让我觉得自己是个傻瓜, Jan.
我真想把"深入追击"的...
...那个Mac McGrath揪出来痛打一顿
听起来不错,但你犯不着和他们一样
你比那些人好一万倍, Deedsy.
所以,不要理会他们
我们永远在这里支持你
谢谢你, Jan.
我叔公开的公司确实非常了不起
他为5万人提供了工作
他还经常做许多好事
这么说, 他是个很不错的人
别忘了, 你很像他!
别再说那些了,说说关于那个女孩儿的事
她很不错, 和我一样, 来自一个小镇
Deeds, 你这个变态的混球....
你还不抓紧时间,不然她就跟别人跑了
Boo-Yah!
他以为是你写的!
- 来吧,Cedar. 打起精神来
- 接球吧
嘿,你想谋杀我呀,你真有两下子!
你约我打球,我以为你会打
Johnny McEnroe 说这玩意儿很简单
而且我叔公也很喜欢,对吧?
- 你怎么知道的?
- 从他日记里读到的
是吗?
我不知道他还写日记
抱歉,伙计
没关系, 那家伙刚加入
球童!
来吧, 我准备好了
你还好吧?
- 小意思 !
- Anderson, 你一定在偷着高兴,是吧?
是的
听着, Deeds, 有个好消息
那些文件明天就可以签字了
一方面,你可以放心,你叔公的公司
有了一个好的归宿...
...同时,你也是一个身价400亿的富翁了.
我正打算,或许多逗留几天...
- 和你们一起开开会什么的
- 什么?
失误!
我想我可以学着管理公司,就像打网球一样
我发誓,我不是有意的
我不是必须卖掉自己的股份,对吧?
还有,Cedar.
我认识了一个女孩儿, 我们很合得来
你们一定很开心
正中咽喉 ? 不会吧 ?
我得问问你, 如果我打中你, 是谁得分?
- 你
- 这么说,我赢了
"浴室面谈 , 关于Deeds"?
老天!
你是谁? 想谈什么?
我是 "深入追击" 的制作人
我有些关于Deeds的消息, 可以帮你把他弄走,
有兴趣么?
好啊,看看你有什么消息,
拜托别洗你的臀部了
- 知道Deeds的女朋友么?
- 那个学校护士
不完全正确
Lucy, 帮我把昨晚的稿子拿来
J.D. 会告诉你在哪儿
喂,你坐在我的椅子上干嘛呢?
Chuck Cedar
或许咱们可以合作一下
- 感觉兴奋么?
- 非常兴奋
- 你带我去哪儿?
- 我说过, 这是个惊喜
怎么样?
"Winchestertonfieldville, 爱荷华"
简直他妈的开玩笑!
我从没听过你说粗话
我太兴奋了!
各位Winchestertonfieldvillians 的居民,
还认得出这个女孩儿吗?
给大家一点提示,
"从Radley家的苹果树上摔下来...
"...胳膊疼的要命!"
快看看,这是小Pammy Dawson呀!
大家好
你和Bill Dawson有什么关系吗?
是的,我们是亲戚
我好像想起来了
你以前是不是有些驼背?
- 没错,那一定是我了,我的确有一点点驼背
- 是吗?
那可不是什么"一点点驼背" !
我说的那个女孩,后背和骆驼差不多
是的,的确是驼背的很厉害,
不过我不太喜欢别人提起罢了
快瞧,Martha, 是"卡西莫多", 长这么大了!
太好了,我还以为你死了呢
她现在是个护士了
- 你是护士?
- 没错
这个毛病该怎么治?
- 还是让Pepper医生来看看吧
- 谁?
非常高兴见到大家, 我们该走了!
再见
- 你好,邮递员先生
- 早上好
你们好吗?
快看, 就是那座了
蓝色的百叶窗, 红色大门 , 轮胎做的秋千
那就是你们家了,对不对?
你这么肯定?
来,去看看
大家好 , 你们知道她是谁吗 ?
她以前在这里住过,那时她还是个小姑娘
是这样的
你们住过同一所房子, 差不多该算是亲戚了
令我想起了很多
从何说起呢?
这是壁炉...
...我父亲会烧木头...
...生火
这是饭厅,我们在这儿吃饭...
...和做饭
这是我弟弟的房间
我父母不喜欢我弟弟
这座房子是我爸爸6年前亲手建的
你爸爸在骗人
你为什么 --
他呛住了, 咱们快走吧
- 救命啊
- 你说什么呀?
- 你是个护士,快帮帮他
- 救救他!
- 让开,孩子们
- 他要死了!
- 送他去医院吧!
- 把它拍出来!
- 救救他!
- 把它弄出来!
救救他, 求你了!
- 真没想到
- 谢谢
我救了他
你真了不起, Dawson护士
谢谢了
- 好厉害的停车技术,伙计
- 谢谢, Deeds.
试音, 试音
我真的太高兴了
谢谢你, 多么美妙的一天
- 谢谢你带我参观你的故乡
- 希望有机会能去你的故乡看看
也许,有一天这里会成为我的新故乡
Deeds.
- 有些事我想告诉你
- 什么事?
怎么了?
回新汉普郡,做个快乐的有钱人吧!
别再...
...别让自己再受到伤害, 好吗?
混蛋
Pam.
我给你写了张卡
可能很愚蠢
但我已经尽了最大的努力, 请不要笑话我
记得那晚我们去餐厅...
...你点了奶酪烤鸡?
所以我给你画了一碟
里面有鸡肉和奶酪...
...还有意大利面条. 弯弯曲曲的
花了我不少时间
很漂亮!
里面还有一首诗!
"无法呼吸, 仿佛身在半空"
"爱意荡漾, 怎将它心中锁"
"如何启齿, 该怎把话儿说"
"毫无保留, 为你燃烧这爱之火"
"手足无措, 那不是真的我"
"与你共舞, 仿佛梦幻中时光交错"
真不错!
"如愿以偿"
"原来,爱的滋味令人着魔"
我找不到其他可以压韵的字
所以只好用了个"魔"字...
对不起, Deeds.
- 我真的很抱歉
- 用不着抱歉 ,我不明白
Hi, Finch小姐.... Atticus.
晚安
- Al, 我走路回去
- 好的, Deeds.
我爱纽约!
没人在乎!
我爱上他了
我今晚会去见他, 把一切都告诉他
- 或许他会揍你一顿的
- 那样我会好过些
别这样, Babe, 振作点
你真的愿意为那个笨蛋而放弃一切吗?
他不是笨蛋, 他心地善良
他之所以被误解,
是因为他并不认同我们那种
冷嘲热讽、漠不关心
- 那种颓废、卑鄙、自作聪明
- 胡说八道?
对，还有胡说八道
好吧，等一会儿, 我会穿上我的名牌大衣
开着昂贵的名车, 回到
我第五大街的豪华公寓...
...然后和我的女朋友风花雪月
全因为刚才你说的那些陋习,
我拥有了这一切
真替你高兴,Mac. 但我还是得告诉他
好吧....
Babe Bennett 坠入爱河了
我为你感到高兴,真的
我会想念你的, Babe.
真舍不得你
她会喜好么?
明白
奶酪烤鸡? 不错,谢谢你!
让我听听
- 她会喜欢的, Deeds先生
- 好的
- Emilio, 布置的真漂亮
- 谢谢你
这些花好像太高了, 我都看不见她了
- 换些小的好吗?
- 好的,先生
Okay.
Byron?
非常好
- 能陪我坐一会儿么?
- 好的,先生
说点什么, 假装你就是她
- 我,先生?
- 求你了
好吧...
...谢谢你今晚邀请我共进晚餐
我很荣幸
你太高了, 能不能坐低一点?
- 像这样?
- 好多了
这是我感觉最美妙的约会
我有一种很特别的感觉
我也是
我有件东西想送给你
来, 靠近一点
- 我非常喜欢你
- 我也喜欢你
- 我每时每刻都在想你
求你, 让我摸摸你的脚吧 !
好了, 到此为止吧, 你可以走了!
- Deeds!
- 伙计们!
今天是你的大日子,我们来助助兴
谢谢你们,我现在紧张死了,
这辈子第一次求婚
现在是7:30, "深入追击"播出的时间
这次不会再有什么令人尴尬的消息了吧?
我想不会的,我整天都在这儿,
什么蠢事都没做过
那我们来看看他们还有什么新花样儿 ?
劳驾!
- 请转到八频道 ?
- 没问题
欢迎收看"深入追击", 我是Mac McGrath.
一直以来, 我们的传媒都有一种值得自豪的能力
那就是对新闻事件十分敏锐和投入
...但同时又能够保持足够的专业距离
但是如果一个记者陷入自己报道的事件而
不能自拔, 又会如何?
如果一个记者爱上了一个白痴呢?
你看到的是Longfellow Deeds 和 Pam Dawson.
- 竟然连她都不放过
- 一个学校护士...
...刚刚从爱荷华州的Winchestertonfieldville镇
移居纽约
慢着! 这位Pam Dawson
好像和 Babe Bennett 惊人的相象 ?
而后者是我们"深入追击"的一位制作人员
事实上 , 她们根本就是一个人
我们将为您送上最新的偷拍影像
Deeds.
我来是想解释清楚
我是全世界最蠢的白痴
这个城市有时是很残忍的
我不属于这里
我不会管理公司, 甚至不会管理自己的生活
别这么说,
还有个好消息, 文件已经准备好了
你一签字, 我们买回股票, 而你得到400亿美元
我不想要, 捐给慈善机构吧
- 哪个比较好?
- 黑人高等教育基金会?
好吧, 就给他们吧
我们送你去机场好吗 ? 让公司的直升机送你回家
多谢了 , 我还是自己走吧
- 很高兴认识大家
- 很高兴认识你, Deeds.
再见!
再见了
怎么会这样!
你一定是Jan了. 我是--
我知道, 你不就是那个五行欠打的Dawson么
那个无情无义的小娼妇!
没错, 骂得对 !
你知道他被你伤害得多深吗?
我决不会让你再骚扰他
我一定要找到他, 无论如何
- 你不妨试试看
- 我要告诉他我有多伤心
就算找遍天涯海角...
无论付出什么代价, 我也要弥补我的过错
真抱歉, 你说什么都没用!
我跟你说, 只要过得了我这关...
...我就告诉你他在哪儿
放马过来 !
来吧小乖乖
我在斗牛场干过6年 ,
你得加把劲才行了
这招怎么样 ?
你踢我那儿干嘛 ?
我又没有 "小弟弟" !
起来 !
- 把我放下 !
- 没问题 !
- 你就告诉我Deeds在哪里吧!
- 你别跑啊
我要把你大卸八块拿去喂狗!
你没事吧 ?
踢得漂亮, 踢得漂亮 !
鬼眼 !
- 给你
花生酱加糖豆, 真是绝配 !
别太难过了, 时间可以医治一切创伤
除了这双鬼眼
是啊, 回家后我感觉好多了
我不是说你, Deeds.
我是对那只松鼠说的
那个叫Cedar的家伙实在不是什么好东西...
...他要分拆你叔公的公司,
解雇所有的员工
你从哪听说的?
我整天都看股市频道
因为我怀疑有个主持人可能
是个邪恶的妖精
他骗得了别人, 骗不了我
是那儿了
来人哪!
救命啊!
Deeds! 救命!
Deeds! 救救我!
上帝啊! Deeds!
Oh, 上帝!
这回摄像机藏在哪儿? 树林里吗?
没有摄像机
我冻死了, 求你!
这次没歹徒袭击你了?
我对...
...对不起你
我是真的爱你
你胡扯!
我来了!
退后点! 退后 !
铁脚来了
不!
抓住我的脚, 别管难不难看了
快上来, 没事了
- 上帝, 你的脚可真恶心!
- 我知道, 我知道, 起来吧
你怎么样? 没事吧 ?
没事
你没从苹果树上摔下来过 ?
没有
但我是真的爱你
可我连你是谁都不知道
对不起
我十分抱歉!
Preston Blake留下的庞大公司
将会四分五裂, 并被拍卖
根据经Chuck Cedar证实的消息,
Blake媒体公司将被分拆后出售
唯一有能力反对Cedar先生, 并挽救
该公司的人---Longfellow Deeds
已经放弃投票权, 离开了纽约
在明天召开的股东大会上,
拍卖公司的决议很可能会顺利通过
另有消息证实,Blake公司的5万名员工...
很可能会失业
慢着, 我也是Blake公司的员工
老天, 太糟糕了!
女士们先生们, 事实上, 这次公司的出售
将会使每个股东, 包括我本人
手中的持有的股份价值不菲
但在投票之前, 根据公司的章程
我必须听取各位股东对该计划的各种意见
有哪位想发言 ?
毁掉这间公司, 是对一个杰出人物的侮辱!
你吓了我一跳
这是无法容忍的可怕罪行
对不起, 我想说两句
Longfellow Deeds.
非常不幸 , 你已经卖掉了自己的300万股份
- 所以你无权在这里发言
- 不幸的是你
我今早买了一股Blake媒体的股份
你告诉过我, 每个股东都有发言权
无论大小
好吧, 给你两分钟
别忘了, 我拥有百分之四十九的股权
所以, 你差不多要说服所有其他股东
...放弃到手的钞票!
大家好,我是 Deeds.
我曾经是本公司最大的股东, 不过只是短短几天
那时我非常富有,大权在握
有钱和权力并不是一件坏事
而且那边的先生们似乎对此极为热衷
但问题是, 如果为了金钱和权力
不择手段会怎么样呢 ?
我不清楚你为什么心血来潮
但你一定是选错了讲道的地方
我想说的是,
你们小时候是否梦想过将来会成为
一个惟利是图的商人 ?
最起码, 我没有
我想当一个消防员
我想作一个帮别人解决困难的人
我希望能帮助别人
当然, 从那些杆子上滑下来也挺有意思
而钱, 我总是最后才考虑
你呢, 先生 ?
你想过当个消防员吗 ?
没有
说实话, 我曾经想当一个兽医
不错, 你为什么想当兽医 ?
- 我希望能帮助生病的动物
- 那你现在是干什么的?
我经营连锁屠宰场
这好像和你的初衷背道而驰了吧?
Okay.
坐在后面的人, 请告诉我你的梦想
我想作一个魔术师 !
- 那你现在做什么?
- 我经营一个色情网站
我想, 那至少也能给某些人带来快乐,
不过不太光彩罢了
- 还有谁 ?
- 我想作个议员
- 我想开花店
- 做闻名世界的煎饼
我想作个男人
原来如此
我想作乒乓球冠军
但是, 你们没有实现自己的梦想, 对不对?
我们一次一次的向现实妥协...
而现在, 你们正打算令5万人失去工作!
只是为了赚点快钱?
如果你们儿时的自己知道了今天的事儿
我敢打赌, 他们一定会把你们折腾个半死
甚至不能容忍你们有这样的想法
没错, 我会把自己痛打一顿
我会让自己从旋转木马上飞出去!
我会把自己赤身裸体绑在椅子上,再用烟头烫 !
这儿有人想过当心理医生吗 ?
开玩笑罢了, 朋友
现在还有机会挽救我们的童真 !
请不要拆分我叔公的公司
我一直都想试试这个
不错...
...说的非常动情, Deeds.
似乎拍卖的决议被否决了 ?
不过我好像忘了一件事
我自己的300万股份...
再加上我为外国投资者代理的5万股
有了这百分之五十一的股份, 我该如何投票呢?
我投赞成票 !
305万票, 赞成!
赞成票获胜, Blake媒体公司不复存在了
别那么着急, Chuck.
你有麻烦了, 我小的时候,
一直想作个好记者
Bennett小姐, 我可不知道你也是股东
你不知道的事儿还多着呢 !
比如说修眉毛
还有, 那就是: 当Deeds 放弃他的财产时,
那些财产其实并不属于他
- 你在说什么?
- 我手头有Preston Blake的日记
是我偷来看的
请别生气, 我是为了干好事 , 我保证
我想在这里读一段Blake先生的日记
日期是: 1957年4月12日
" 我的欲望就要爆发
" 依靠心灵的指引, 我取得了事业的成功 "
" 如今, 它要再一次帮助我 "
" 寻找真爱 ! "
"只要她给我一个暗示, 一个机会"
要我帮您擦擦这些树叶么,Blake先生?
你可以叫我Preston
要我帮您擦树叶么, Preston?
好的
好的 ！
那位神秘的女士是谁 ?
这是Blake公司1957年4月的出入登记本
12号那晚, 只有一个女工在Blake所在的那层上班
不幸的是, 9个月之后, 她就去世了,
死于难产 !
留下了一个男孩...
...那天是1958年1月23日
那是我的生日!
Consuela Lopez小姐
那是我母亲!
你才是400亿美元遗产的合法继承人!
那是我的钱 ?
只需要一个简单的 DNA 测试就能证明
Emilio Lopez 才是Blake媒体公司的最大股东
- 那是我的钱!
- 是你的钱!
是我的钱 !
我会为大家办好事的
免费佛来明哥舞课程 !
各位, 各位! 请静一静!
- 那是我的钱
- 别被误导, 那都是骗人的
Cedar...
... 你被解雇了
你无权解雇我 !
我才是老板 !
放开我 ! 我是 Chuck Cedar!
那次, 在湖上你救了我...
我还没机会谢谢你
- 别客气
- 你说你还不知道我是谁
我突然意识到, 连我自己都不知道
于是我决定要重新认识自己,
这是我目前的成果:
我叫Babe Bennett.
我出生在长岛的Syossett
我的眼睛是褐色, 不过我已经不记得
头发原来的颜色了
5年级时, 我极度崇拜Walter Cronkite.
我跟你说的那个小本子是真的
我喜欢Bruce Springsteen, Almond Roca的歌
还有Abbott 和 Costello 演的电影
我不喜欢甘草和自己的脚踝
最重要的是, 我明白自己干了蠢事
我愿意用一辈子的时间...
来请求你再给我一次机会
因为我深深的爱着你
我知道那是永远不变的爱
你一定是疯了
你的脚踝很漂亮
咱们回家吧
你被解雇了! 还有你 ! 你 ! 你 !
Oh, 你,先生, 我一定要炒了你
我希望能留下, 如果能再有一次机会,
我会做些好事的
可以不解雇, 但明早你要让我帮你换袜子
好的
至于你, Long-Long-Longfellow...
是你让这一切成为现实的
以你美妙的话语和善良的心灵
还有Bennett小姐, 了不起的调查工作
我该怎么感谢你呢 ?
有你的友谊就足够了, Emilio.
你是个好人
我会想你的
Deeds!
- 我给你10亿美元好吗 ?
- 好吧
成交
天哪!
难以置信!
- 什么事?
- Hallmark公司的回信
他们真的要买我的一张卡
- 太好了! 是哪张?
- 我写给你的那张, 还记得吗?
我记得吗 ?
"无法呼吸, 仿佛身在半空"
"爱意荡漾, 怎将它心中锁"
"如何启齿, 该怎把话儿说"
"毫无保留, 为你燃烧这爱之火"
"手足无措, 那不是真的我"
"与你共舞, 仿佛梦幻中时光交错"
"如愿以偿"
"原来,爱的滋味令人着魔"
我以你为荣!
简直不敢相信, Deeds给我们每人买了一辆
妈的, 这玩意儿真够快的!
我没事儿!